你也会飘着
You'll float, too!
(1989年 九月)
我看到了我们几个
I saw all of us.
所有人都在
All of us were there.
回到了那个下水道里
Back in the cistern.
但我们都长大了
But we were older.
到了我们爸妈的年龄
We were our parents' ages.
我长大成人之后还是这么帅吗
Am I still handsome as an adult?
反正你就长成了那样
You grow into your looks.
那他妈是啥意思
What the fuck does that mean?
我呢
What about me?
和现在差不多
Like now,
但是高了
but taller.
发誓吧
Swear it.
发誓如果它没死
Swear if It isn't dead,
如果它又回来
if It ever comes back,
我们也会回来
we'll come back, too.
记忆
Memory,
真是个有趣的东西
it's a funny thing.
人们总是愿意相信
People want to believe they are...
他们是他们所记得的那个人
what they choose to remember.
美好的东西
The good stuff.
那些时刻
The moments.
那些地方
The places.
我们坚持自己就是这样的人
The people we all hold on to.
但有些时候
But sometimes...
有些时候
sometimes...
正是我们希望遗忘的部分造就了我们
we are what we wish we could forget.
(27年后)
好了 孩子们
Okay, kids.
准备好了吗
Get ready.
开始
Go!
会是谁呢
Who's it gonna be?
第一个把气球弄爆的人就是赢家
First one to pop their balloon's a winner!
我可说不好冠军是谁哦 有位参赛者
It could be anyone! We got a real...
- 风头很强啊 - 加油加油加油
- barn burner here, folks. - Come on. Come on. Come on.
胜利就在眼前
It's getting close.
有没有人能追上他呢
Who's gonna catch the leader, huh?
谁会成为今晚的大赢家呢
Who's gonna be the big winner tonight?
- 太好了 - 喔
- Oh, yeah! - Whoo!
大吉大利 今晚吃鸡
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
- 谢谢 - 喔
- Thank you. - Wow.
你可真是大出风头
You really showed 'em, huh?
那可不是
I did. I...
耶
Yeah.
小姑娘 你想要这个吗
Hey, girl, do you want this?
谢谢你让我赢了
Thanks for letting me win.
是啊
Yeah.
你赢了个什么 维姬
What'd you get, Vicky?
真是绅士呢
Aww. Such a gentleman.
看看这个
Look at that!
这个是你的安慰奖
Well, here is your consolation prize.
看看这个
Look at that.
虽然我从来不喜欢河狸
Never been a fan of the beaver,
但是这顶帽子吧 还挺不错
but look at this hat. I mean...
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们得谈谈物流工作
So, we need to talk logistics.
真浪漫啊
How romantic.
浪漫
Romantic?
什么他妈的这么浪漫呀
What's so fucking romantic, huh?
嘿
Hey.
你妈没有教过你怎么对付
Your mommas ever teach you boys to respond to someone...
向你问愚蠢问题的人吗
when they ask you a fucking question?
算了吧 艾德里安
Come on, Adrian.
你有什么问题吗 死基佬
You got a problem, faggot?
我倒是没有 但梅格·瑞恩可能有
I don't, but Meg Ryan called.
她可是想把她的假发要回去呢
She wants her wig back.
行了 行了
All right. All right.
算了吧 艾德里安
Come on. Come on, Adrian.
这就是为什么
Stuff like that...
我要离开这个糟糕的小镇
is why I have to leave this shithole town.
思想狭隘
Small minds.
他们的屌也挺小的
They have small dicks.
我是认真的
I'm being serious.
我们不属于这里
We belong elsewhere.
但如果你不喜欢纽约的话
Hey, look, if you end up hating New York,
我们也可以搬回这里
we can always move back here.
我只是想和你在一起
I just want to be with you.
我才不在乎是在纽约还是在德利镇
I don't care. New York, Derry, whatever. It's...
你嘴可真甜
You have to say that.
我才不是花言巧语
I don't have to say anything.
把那顶帽子摘下来
Take off that fucking hat.
- 天哪 - 算了 我们走吧
- Oh, God. - Come on, let's go.
我们可不想给人们留下这种印象
Wouldn't want to give people the impression...
我们竟然任由你俩这种死基佬在镇上游荡
we allow a bunch of fucking fairies like you in this town.
他就出生在这里 傻逼
Yeah, he was born here, asshole.
- 算了 我们走吧 - 不 你知道吗
- All right, let's go. - No. You know what?
我可以为你把帽子摘下来
I'll take off the hat for you.
可干嘛止步于此呢
But why leave it there?
今晚你还有什么
Anything else you would like me...
想让我脱下来的东西吗
to take off for you tonight?
有什么特殊需求嘛 小姐们
Any special requests, ladies?
傻逼
Fucker!
放开他
Let him go!
- 这是什么 - 住手
- What's that? - Stop.
我可不觉得你需要它
I don't think you'll be needing that.
- 离他远点 - 打他
- Leave him alone! - Hit him.
他有哮喘 你这个混账
He's got asthma, fucker!
动手啊
Come on!
往死里打
Fuck him up!
动脚踢他呀
Come on, kick him!
快点 把他踢个屁股尿流
Come on, kick the shit out of him.
艾德里安
Adrian!
我还是他妈的很讨厌你的发型
I still hate your fucking hair.
艾德里安
Adrian!
他妈的离他远点
Get the fuck off him!
看看你把他的蠢脸搞成啥样了
Look what you did to his fucking face!
帮我把他架起来
Hey! Hey! Help me get him up.
艾德里安
Adrian.
帮我把这个小嬉皮架起来 快点的
Help me get this fucking punk up right now.
把那个帽子给我 克里斯
Give me the hat, Chris.
这他妈的是我的
It's fucking mine!
我说了把他妈的帽子给我
I said give me the fucking hat!
艾德里安
Adrian!
你喜欢那样吗
You like that?
欢迎来到德利镇 傻逼
Welcome to Derry, motherfucker.
不 艾德里安
No! Adrian!
不
No!
赶紧离开这
Let's get the fuck out of here.
- 走啊 - 不
- Let's go! - No!
艾德里安
Adrian!
救命
Help!
救命啊
Help me!
来人啊
Somebody!
来人救救我啊
Somebody fucking help me!
艾德里安
Adrian.
不
No!
艾德里安
Adrian!
我们都在下面飘着
We all float down here!
事实上
Thing is,
有时候 我们希望自己遗忘的东西
sometimes what we wish was forgotten,
我们试着留在过去的东西
what we tried to leave in the past,
不会停留原地
won't stay there.
警员们 请答复
Units, please respond.
我们收到报告 发现了一具被肢解的尸体
I'm getting reports of a body found dismembered.
收到 你是说"被肢解"吗
Come back. Was that "dismembered"?
是的
That's affirmative.
案发现场在狂欢节
Scene is near the south entrance...
南部的入口
of the festival grounds.
收到 警车已出动了
Copy that. En route.
要封锁交通吗
Any directive for TC?
是的
That's affirmative.
警长说封锁德利镇街道大桥
Chief said to tape off the Derry Street Bridge.
有时候 它会回来找你
Sometimes, it comes back for you.
(回家吧 回家吧 回家吧)
《小丑回魂2》
(阁楼)
丹柏先生 他们需要您去一下拍摄现场
Mr. Denbrough? They need you on set.
走这条路吧
We're just going to go this way.
- 我要钻过去 我要钻过去 - 别啊
- I'm doing it. I'm doing it. - No, don't!
嘿 离门远点啊
Hey! Clear the door!
拜托 你没看过《夺宝奇兵》吗
Oh, come on. You've never seen Indiana Jones?
看路啊
Watch your back.
你是剧组成员吗
Hey, hey. You a crewmember?
我是作者
I'm the writer.
你老公来了
Your husband's here.
你写好了吗
Hey! Do you have the pages?
所有人 远离起重机
Everyone, keep clear of the crane.
我的朋友 电影需要一个结尾
My friend, a film needs an ending.
- 你知道这一点 对吧 - 是啊
- You do know that, right? - Oh, yeah.
你说再给你一天
You said that you needed another day...
你就能写好了
to finish the pages,
但是我们今晚就该拍了
and we're shooting this thing. It's tonight.
那只有17小时了
That's, like, 17 hours...
大家都冷静一下 好吗
Everybody, calm down, okay?
我很冷静
I'm calm.
我希望这个电影能拍的让你开心
I want you to be happy with the movie.
你懂不懂我是站在你这边的
You understand? I'm on your side.
那真是太好了 因为在我书里的结局…
That's great. 'Cause in my book, the ending...
非常糟糕
Is terrible.
无意冒犯 人们爱过你的书 爱过
All due respect, people loved your book. Loved.
但他们都讨厌结局
They hated the ending.
你说过你喜欢我的结局来着
You said you liked the ending.
骗你的
That was a lie.
- 我们要做得更好 好吗 - 好吧
- We gotta do better, okay? - Yeah.
奥德拉 你懂我意思 能不能和他说说
Audra, you have my notes. Would you...
好的 十分感谢 请送我回一号位
Okay, thank you very much. Take me back to one, please.
再见
Bye.
你懂他意思
You have his notes?
他说的没错
He's not wrong.
你也不喜欢吗
You hate my endings, too?
不是所有结局
Not all your endings.
但这个
But this...
- 行吧 - 只是
- Okay. - Just...
怎么了 你难道想让我一直骗你
What? Do you want me to keep lying to you...
- 就因为我是你的老婆 - 你是我老婆吗
- just because I'm your wife? - You're my wife?
不是 不过你知道吗
No. No. But you know what?
你过去八年来一直在激怒我的边缘试探
You've been blowing smoke up my ass for eight years?
我想你有时候不是你自己吧
I guess I thought you were someone else.
我没有激怒你过
I have not been blowing smoke up your ass.
所有人都喜欢幸福结局
Everybody wants a happy ending.
所有人都想要个大团圆
Everybody wants closure.
但是生活往往不是这样的
But that's not the way life works out.
想想彼得想要什么 电影公司想要什么吧
I think what Peter wants and what the studio wants...
电影公司 你什么时候成个商人了
The studio? When'd you become a company man?
天哪 你是个艺术家啊
Jesus, you're an artist.
拜托 以我写的方式去演
Come on. What's wrong with just doing it...
到底怎么了 以我想要的方式去演
the way it's written? The way I wanted.
当那个我想让你当的女人到底有什么错
What's wrong with being the woman I want you to be?
去你妈的 比尔
Fuck you, Bill.
我是说剧本里的那个角色 不是说你
On the page. The part, I mean. Not you.
你好
Hello?
比尔·丹柏吗 我是迈克
Bill Denbrough? It's Mike.
哪个迈克
Mike who?
迈克·韩洛
Mike Hanlon.
德利镇的
From Derry.
你需要回家一趟
You need to come home.
艾迪 我一直在和你说
Eddie, I keep telling you...
不要这样吓我
not to scare me like this.
可你从来不听我的
And you never listen to me.
玛拉 拜托 现在不行
All right. Myra, please. Not now.
你现在不该出去的
You shouldn't be out there.
艾迪 你现在开车不安全
Eddie, it's not safe to drive...
路面还很湿滑呢
when the roads are slick like this.
甜心 三小时前
Sweetheart, it stopped raining, like,
雨就停了 好吗
three hours ago. All right?
不会出事的
Everything is gonna be fine.
妈的 傻逼 懂不懂交规啊
Hey, dickhead! Flow of traffic mean anything to you?
如果你打滑失控了呢
What if you hydroplane?
我不会打滑失控的
I'm not gonna hydroplane.
评估风险是我的工作
It is my job to assess risk.
所以我说你就信
So, please trust me when I tell you...
从统计学上来讲
that, statistically speaking,
我现在出交通事故的风险要高得多
I am much more likely to get into an accident...
因为我正在边开车边和你打电话
because I am talking to you on the phone!
行吗 我得挂了
All right? I have to go.
回头再说 再见
I will talk to you soon. Goodbye.
我是艾德华·卡斯布拉克
Edward Kaspbrak speaking.
你没有像平时一样说
You didn't say, "Okay, bye, I love you,"
"好的再见 我爱你"
Like you usually do.
听着 没法聊了
Listen to me. I can't!
我开会要…
I'm going to be late to this...
(来电等待 缅因州 德利镇)
迟到了
meeting.
说"我爱你" 艾迪
Say "I love you," Eddie.
好的 我爱你妈妈
Okay, I love you, Mommy.
什么
What?
玛拉 再见
Myra. Bye.
你好 哪位
Hello? Who's this?
是我 迈克
It's me. Mike.
哪个迈克
Mike who?
艾迪 你还好吗
Eddie! You okay?
好得很
Yeah, I'm pretty good.
哥们 什么鬼
Dude! Dude, what the fuck?
你五秒钟前还好好的呢
You were fine, like, five seconds ago.
是谁啊 谁打来的
Who was it? Who called? Huh?
瑞奇 说话啊
Rich? Rich? Talk to me.
还有两分钟你就该上台了 你还好吗
You're on in two minutes. You good?
因为你看上去可不咋好
'Cause you look not good.
- 我没事 - 你没事 很好
- I'm fine. - You're fine? Okay.
我们来了 我们来了
And we're walking. We're walking.
还有60秒
Sixty seconds.
走快点 好吗
Even faster. All right.
给他拿瓶水
Can we get him a bottle of water, maybe?
- 波旁威士忌 - 波旁威士忌 行 行
- Bourbon. - Bourbon. Sure, sure.
再来个薄荷糖
And a mint.
要开始了
It is showtime.
- 我觉得我不行 - 你要做
- I don't think I can do this. - It's what you do.
- 真快啊 - 你行的 你牛逼得很
- That was fast. - You kill. You're a killer.
好了 我们可以上台了
Okay. We are good to go, and...
我们往哪走 往哪走
Hey! Where we going? Where we going?
不 这边走 乖孩子
No. This way. Attaboy.
好了
Okay.
好了 我看上去怎么样
All right. How do I look?
你的手在抖 瑞奇
Your hands are shaking, Rich.
妈的
Shit.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
有请瑞奇·托兹
please welcome Richie Tozier!
好了 大家今晚怎么样
All right. How are we doing tonight?
我的女朋友抓到我
So, my girlfriend caught me masturbating...
对着她朋友的脸书主页打飞机
to her friend's Facebook page.
所以我现在加入了一个手淫者匿名互助会
And so now I'm in Masturbators Anonymous.
第一次参会的时候我站了起来
And I stand up at the first meeting...
我说:"我的名字是瑞奇·嘴臭"
and I say, "My name is Richie Trashmouth. "
- 嘴臭 - 闭嘴 瑞奇
- Trashmouth. - Shut up, Richie.
- 该死的色狼 - 闭嘴 瑞奇
- Fucking perv. - Shut up, Richie.
傻逼
Pussy!
嘴臭…
Trashmouth. Uh...
我把笑话忘了
Forgot the joke.
你真垃圾
You suck!
女士们先生们 谢谢你们
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
给我们今天这次展示的机会
for letting us present to you today.
这栋建筑包含上百万平方米的
Now, this will include over a million square feet...
商业和住宅空间
of commercial and residential space.
最先进的办公大楼
State-of-the-art office towers.
其实我想要搞明白的是
What I'm really looking for is to understand...
我们如何去创造更多的零售商机
how we create even more retail opportunities.
如果我们在这里 这里都建墙
If we put in walls here and all along here...
不要墙
Lose them.
无意冒犯 汉斯康先生
With all due respect, Mr. Hanscom...
请叫我本 我也无意冒犯你们
Ben, please. And with all due respect to you,
但是光看着这个模型
I'm getting claustrophobic...
我都要犯幽闭恐惧症了 你们不是吗
just looking at this model. Aren't you?
听着 建更多的墙 只会让这个地方更像一座监狱
Look. Throw up more walls, it's gonna feel like a prison.
你们知道监狱里的人想做什么吗
You know what people want to do in prison?
想出去啊
Get out. Right?
这应该是个能让人们聚集的地方
This should be a place that brings people together.
一处汇聚之地
A meeting ground.
像是俱乐部会所
A clubhouse.
如果
And if,
人们在这里的时候
while people are there...
(迈克)
失陪一小会儿
Excuse me for one second.
- 你好 - 本
- Hello? - Ben?
我是德利镇的迈克·韩洛
It's Mike Hanlon. From Derry.
我要不要直接订了
Should I just book it?
你确定你工作能请下来假吗
You're sure you can get away from work?
那可是夏天 当然
It's summer, why not?
行了 那就锁定布宜诺斯艾利斯了
Okay, we are Buenos Aires-bound.
我是史丹利·尤瑞斯
Stanley Uris speaking.
我是迈克
It's Mike.
哪位
I'm sorry?
迈克·韩洛
Mike Hanlon.
德利镇的
From Derry.
迈克
Mike.
天啊 对不起 你好啊
God, sorry. Yes, hi.
我没有 我不知道为什么我
I don't know why I didn't...
过去多久了
How long's it been?
很久了
A long time.
27年
27 years.
它回来了 是不是
It's come back, hasn't it?
这就是你给我打电话的原因吧
That's why you're calling me?
又开始了 史丹
It's starting again, Stan.
坏事又开始发生了
Bad things are happening.
你给其他人打电话了吗
Did you call the others?
我是说 如果他们不来呢
I mean, what if they don't come?
我们发过誓的 你还记得吗
We made a promise, remember?
你什么时候能回来
How soon can you get here?
那个
Well, I...
我可能还有几件事要做
Yeah, I would need to do a few things...
明天行吗
Tomorrow.
我们没有多少时间了
We don't have much time.
我会把一切你需要的都短信发给你
I'll text you everything you need.
到时候见 史丹
I'll see you soon, Stan the Man.
你发誓吗
Do you swear?
我发誓 比尔
I swear, Bill.
(缅因州德利镇)
你发下了誓言 贝弗莉
You made a promise, Beverly.
我很抱歉 迈克
I'm so sorry, Mike.
我真的记不太清了
I don't even really remember.
你难道没有好奇过为什么你记不起来
Haven't you ever wondered why you can't seem...
一些常人都能记住的事情
to remember the things most people should...
你来自哪里 你究竟是谁
about where they're from, about who they are,
为什么你手上会有那么一道伤疤
why you have that scar on your hand?
其他人也都不记得了
No one else remembered, either.
艾迪 本 史丹 瑞奇
Eddie, Ben, Stan, Richie...
比尔
Bill.
你必须回来
You have to come back.
你们都必须回来
You all do.
什么时候
When?
你没事吧 发生了什么
Are you okay? What's going on?
现在可是大半夜 而你在收拾东西
It's the middle of the night. You're packing?
我不想吵醒你 宝贝
I didn't want to wake you, honey.
我知道这周你已经很累了
I know this week's been really exhausting.
我只是接到了德利镇一个老朋友的电话
I just got a phone call from an old friend from Derry.
我得回到那里去
I have to go back there.
我真的很难解释清楚
It's really hard to explain why.
没事的
It's okay.
你没必要向我做出解释 放松点
You don't have to explain yourself to me. Relax.
我相信你
I trust you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我只是不知道你为什么要对我撒谎
I just don't understand why you'd lie to me.
我听到了
I heard you.
你说了个叫迈克的名字
You said the name Mike.
是啊 是我的朋友
Yes, my friend.
那时我们好几个人一起玩
See, there was a group of us back then,
我们还是小孩子的时候 互相许下了承诺
and we all made a promise to each other when we were kids.
你知道我们这段关系里 信任就是一切吧
You know trust is everything in a relationship.
你知道这对我来说就是一切 对吧
You know it's everything to me, right?
- 我知道 这不是… - 对吗
- I know. This isn't... - Right?
什么 上一次吗
What? Like the last time?
我从未背叛过你
I never cheated on you.
你可真不会撒谎
You're a bad fucking liar,
贝贝
Bev.
你哪也去不成 知道吗
You're not going anywhere, okay?
我就要你待在这里
I want you to stay right here,
然后向我展示
and you're gonna show me...
你本来要和迈克做一些什么勾当
what it is you're gonna do with Mike. Okay?
你弄疼我了 亲爱的
You're hurting me, honey.
没人会像我这样爱你
No one else is gonna love you like me.
你知道的 对吧
You know that, right?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
- 别把这事搞得更难堪 - 不要
- Don't make this fucking harder! - Don't.
没有我你什么都不是 你心里清楚的吧
You're nothing without me! You know that, right?
告诉我我错了啊
Tell me I'm wrong!
(鲍尔斯)
天啊
Jesus Christ.
伙计们
Boys.
不得不说 这个小混蛋还真有种
Little prick's got balls, I'll give him that.
别再往前走了 鲍尔斯
Far enough, Bowers!
我还没完呢
I'm not done yet.
我还没完呢 我还没他妈的完呢
I'm not done. I'm not fucking done.
- 跪下 - 我不能
- On your knees. - I can't. No!
我要把他们都杀了 操 操
I gotta kill them all! Fuck, fuck!
我要把他们都杀了 住手
Fucking kill them all! Stop it!
- 把这个傻逼给我铐起来 - 去你妈的
- Cuff this sorry sack of shit! - Fuck you!
去你妈的
Fuck you!
亨利·鲍尔斯 你因为谋杀
Henry Bowers, I am placing you under arrest...
奥斯卡·鲍尔斯而被拘捕
for the murder of Oscar Bowers.
听见了吗 小混球
Do you understand, dipshit?
你有权要求请律师
You have the right to an attorney.
你也有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
鲍尔斯
Bowers!
鲍尔斯 他妈的安分点
Bowers, calm the fuck down!
看起来今天有人需要更大计量的氯氮平啊
Someone needs a little extra clozapine today, don't they?
他妈的待在你屋子里吧
Stay in your fucking room.
霍克斯塔德
Hockstetter.
我的刀
My knife.
(东方翡翠)
- 哇哦 - 请小心台阶
- Whoa. - Careful.
这边请
This way.
谢谢你
Thanks a lot.
- 嘿 - 哦
- Hey. - Oh...
- 迈克 你看上去真不错 - 比尔
- Mike, you look good. - Bill.
最近怎么样
Hey. How you doing?
比尔
Bill.
我都不知道你们会不会…
I didn't know if any of you would...
毕竟过去这么久了
I mean, after all this time...
- 是啊 - 但是你肯定来了
- Yeah. - But of course you came.
誓言就是誓言
You know, an oath is an oath.
废柴们
Losers...
应该相互照应
gotta stick together, right?
废柴俱乐部
The Losers.
你还记得 真好
You remember that. That's good.
你还记得什么吗
What else do you remember?
我对大豆过敏
I am allergic to soy,
对鸡蛋过敏 蛋白质过敏
anything that has egg in it, uh, gluten,
如果我吃了腰果 我真的会死
and if I eat a cashew, I could realistically die.
我的天啊
Holy shit.
这东西需要密码吗
Is there a password or something?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
那个新来的
The new kid.
本
Ben?
是啊
Yeah.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
真的好久不见
It's been so long.
一直酷下去吧 社会课上的本
Stay cool, Ben from soc class.
你也是 贝弗莉
You too, Beverly.
坚挺住 街区里新来的小孩
Hang tough, new kid on the block.
哇哦
Wow.
帅哥美女
You two look amazing.
我他妈的混成什么样了
What the fuck happened to me?
- 怎么了 哥们 - 嘿 哥们
- What's going on, man? - Hey, man.
- 我是瑞奇 - 我是本
- It's Richie. Hi. - Yeah. It's Ben.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
废柴俱乐部的见面会
This meeting of the Losers' Club...
正式开始了
has officially begun.
看看这些家伙
Look at these guys.
本
Ben.
等等 艾迪 所以你结婚了
So, wait, Eddie, you got married?
这有什么好笑的 混球
Yeah, why's that so fucking funny, dickwad?
是和女人结婚的吗
What? To, like, a woman?
哥们 去你的
Fuck you, bro.
去你的
Fuck you!
行了 那你呢 臭嘴 你结婚了吗
All right. What about you, Trashmouth? You married?
瑞奇不可能结婚的
There's no way Richie's married.
不 我真结婚了
No, I got married.
- 瑞奇 我不相信 - 什么时候
- Richie, I don't believe it. - When?
- 你没听说吗 - 没
- Did you not hear this? - No.
你不知道我结婚了吗
You didn't know I got married?
- 不知道 - 我和你妈妈现在
- No. - Yeah, no. Me and your mom...
非常非常幸福
are very, very happy right now.
非常的幸福啊
Yeah, very happy.
- 他真的信了 - 多谢
- He totally fell for it! - Thanks.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
她可甜了 有时候她还会抱住我
She's very sweet. Sometimes, she'll put her arm around me,
在我耳边低语 就像这样
and she'll whisper to me, she'll go...
我们都听懂了 因为我妈体型巨大异常肥胖
We all get it. My mom was a great, big, fat person.
真好笑 真让人抓狂
Hilarious. Hysterical.
是啊 这块表不错
Yeah, it's a nice watch.
我们来谈谈不再是"庞然大物"的家伙吧
Wait, let's talk about the elephant not in the room...
本
Ben.
什么鬼啊 哥们
What the fuck, man?
好了好了 显然我瘦了几斤
Okay, okay. Obviously, I lost a few pounds.
- 瘦了几斤 - 呵呵可不是嘛
- Lost a few pounds? - Yeah, no shit you lost...
- 瘦了几斤 - 你现在 你可真性感
- a few pounds. - You're, like... You're hot!
确实
That's true.
你就像是所有的巴西足球运动员的
No, you're like every Brazilian soccer player...
集合体啊
wrapped up into one person.
- 完美 - 别说了 你让他尴尬了
- Gorgeous. - Leave him alone. You're embarrassing him.
行了 行了 拜托了
Okay, okay, all right. Please, come on.
史丹利到底来不来啊
Is Stanley coming or what?
快来人救我啊
Someone save me.
史丹
Stan.
Stan...
史丹利·尤瑞斯
Stan Uris. Stan Urine.
史丹利·尤瑞斯 不 他是个怂包
Stanley Urine. No, no, he's a fucking pussy.
他不会来的
He's not gonna show.
不过为什么史丹利会救你
Why would Stanley save you, anyway?
难道不是我在你身上
Was I not the one who basically...
动的手术嘛
performed surgery on you...
- 在鲍尔斯划破你肚子的时候 - 对
- after Bowers cut you up? - Yes!
我的天啊 对啊
Holy shit! That's right.
小艾 别告诉我你最后真成了医生
Please tell me you ended up becoming a doctor, Eds.
没有 我现在是个风险评估师
No, I ended up becoming a risk analyst.
听上去挺有意思
Oh, that sounds really interesting.
具体是做什么的
What does that entail?
我为一些大保险公司工作 然后
Yeah, so I work for a big insurance firm and...
去你妈的 哥们 去你的
Fuck you, dude. Fuck you.
这工作跟有趣沾边吗
Was this job invented before fun?
- 一点都不好笑 - 很好笑啊
- That's so not funny. - It is funny.
你他妈在笑什么
What the fuck are you laughing at?
我建议干一杯吧
I propose a toast...
敬废柴
to the Losers.
脱掉衣服打啵吧
Let's take our shirts off and kiss!
- 来了 - 谢谢
- Oh, here we go. - Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
罗根-马什 我老婆衣柜有一半
Like, Rogan-Marsh, half my wife's closet Rogan-Marsh?
都是这个牌子 很大牌
That's... That's huge.
那是我和我老公汤姆公司下的支线品牌
That's our line. Me and my husband, Tom.
你结婚多久了
How long have you been married?
我们看过你的电影
Hey, we saw your movie,
- 顺便说一句 - 真的吗
- by the way. - You did?
- 天啊 很好看 - 天啊 很好看吧
- Oh, my God! It was so good. - Oh, my God. So good.
很吓人
It was so scary.
结局很烂吗
And the ending sucked?
是的 不好意思
Yeah, it did. I'm sorry.
没事
That's all right.
怎么
What?
没事 就是很奇怪
Nothing. This is just weird.
是啊
Yeah.
一切都很奇怪 这些人和回忆
Just all this, all these memories,
我甚至都不记得发生过
people that I don't even remember forgetting.
很奇怪对吧
I mean, it's weird, right?
我们回来后
Now that we're all here,
想起的东西越来越多
everything just comes back faster and faster.
我是说 所有
I mean, all of it.
是啊
Yeah.
迈克打给我的时候 我吐了
Yeah, you know, when Mike called me, I threw up.
很奇怪对吧 我没由来的紧张反胃
Isn't that weird? Like, I got nervous.
我就犯恶心 吐了
I got, like, sick and I threw up.
现在好了
I feel fine now.
回来和你们坐在一起我觉得轻松多了
I feel very relieved to be here with you guys.
你们为什么这么看我
Why is everybody looking at me like this?
迈克打给我的时候 我撞车了
When Mike called me, I crashed my car.
- 真的假的 - 真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
我听到迈克声音时
Shit, man, I hear you.
我的心脏就像真的
I mean, my heart was literally...
要跳出胸腔一样
pounding right out of my chest.
- 我还以为只有我这样 - 就好像是纯粹的
- I thought it was only me. - It was like pure...
恐惧
Fear.
你们感受到的 就是恐惧
It's fear. What you felt.
我们为什么会有这种感觉 迈克
Why did we all feel like that, Mike?
你是不是记得一些我们忘记的事情 迈克
You remember something we don't, don't you, Mike?
你们离开镇子时 童年记忆开始模糊
Something happens to you when you leave this town.
离得越远 越记不清
The farther away, the hazier it all gets.
只有我没离开过
But me, I never left.
是的
So, yeah.
我记得
I remember.
所有事情
I remember all of it.
潘尼怀斯
Pennywise.
那个该死的小丑
Oh, the fucking clown.
- 我靠 - 潘尼怀斯
- Oh, shit. - Pennywise.
迈克 你说想要我们帮忙
Mike, you said you wanted our help with something.
是什么事
What was that?
在德利镇 每27年
There's an echo here in Derry...
历史就会重演一次
that bounces back every 27 years.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你先听着
Hold on. Listen, listen.
那时我们以为杀死了它
We thought we stopped It back then.
以为一切结束
We thought It was done, but...
迈克
Mike.
一周前 有个叫艾德里安的男人被杀了
A week ago, a man, adrian Mellon, slaughtered.
前阵子晚上 有个叫丽萨·奥布里齐的女孩失踪了
A girl, Lisa Albrecht, the other night, went missing.
好了
All right.
还有别的案例 之后还有会有更多
There've already been others, and there will be more.
我不想听这些话
I don't want to hear about this shit.
- 更多的死亡 更多的痛苦 - 冷静点 没事的
- More death. More pain. - Calm down. It's okay.
我们再干一杯
Let's get another drink.
让他解释 让他解释
Let him explain. Let him explain.
你解释啊 迈克
Explain it to us, Mike.
那个轮回
That echo,
我们可能改变了它
we might have changed It,
就像它改变了我们
just like It changed us.
可我们没能阻止它
But we didn't stop It.
因为它又重演了
Because It just bounced back.
我们发过誓
We made an oath.
所以我才召集你们回来 所以你们才坐在这里
That's why I brought you back. That's why you're here.
将它斩草
To finish It.
除根
For good.
你说的有点暗黑啊
Well, that shit got dark fast.
多谢了 迈克
Thanks, Mike.
我的幸运饼干是"会"
My fortune cookie just says "Could. "
他们这里的幸运饼干不正宗
They don't know how to do fortune cookies here.
我的是"猜"
Mine just says "Guess. "
把纸条放我这来
You wanna throw that over here?
你的是什么 迈克
What you got, Mikey?
等等 什么
Wait, what?
这就是我说的事情
This is what I'm talking about.
"猜-割-不-会-它"
"Guess. Cut. Not. Could. It. "
是一条信息
It's a message.
不 "猜它会不会割"
No, "Guess it could not cut. "
为什么是"猜它会不会割"
Why would it guess it could not cut?
- 割什么 - "猜它会不会割"
- Cut what? - "Guess it could not cut. "
这是什么意思
I don't know what that mean.
- "它"在前 在这里 - "它不可能猜到"
- "It" goes in front. There. - "It could not guess. "
- 它不可能猜到 - "可能它"
- It couldn't guess. - "Could it..."
不是 "它可能不会割吗"
No. "Could it not cut. "
这个"它"说的是不是小丑
When it says "It," Is it talking about It?
- 好了 - 是那个意思吗 "它"是小丑吗
- Yeah. All right. - Is that what it means? Is "It" It?
什么意思 迈克 这是什么意思
What's it? Mike. Where does this go?
这就是我说的事情
That's what I'm talking about.
它…可能…
It... It could...
我不知道这他妈什么意思
I don't know what it fucking means!
是你动了幸运饼干吗 迈克
You fuck with the fortune cookies, Mike?
- 不是 - 让他说 哥们
- No. - Whoa. Let him speak, man.
不是我做的 是它做的
This is not me. This is what It does.
我的吸入器去哪了
I need my fucking inhaler!
你为什么要搞我们 你为什么要给我们打电话
What is wrong with you, man? Why'd you call us?
- 这不好笑 - 这不好笑
- This is not fucking funny! - This is so not funny!
- 贝弗莉 - 这不好笑
- Beverly? - This is so not funny.
(史丹利)
(猜猜史丹利会不会割腕)
为什么会说史丹利
Why does it say Stanley?
有谁他妈的能回答我吗
Someone else fucking answer me!
我靠
Holy shit.
那他妈是什么
What the fuck is that, man?
我的天
Oh, my God.
哇哦
Whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
我的天
Shit.
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
幸运饼干在瞪着我
That fortune cookie's looking at me! Shit!
我要离开这 我呆不下去了
I don't want to be here. I can't fucking do this.
我要回家 我不想呆在这
I wanna go home! I don't wanna be here!
我不想呆在这
I don't wanna be here!
我要回家 我不想呆在这
I wanna go home! I don't wanna be here!
天哪
Holy shit!
该死的
Hey! God damn it.
艾迪
Hey, Eddie!
我操
Whoa! Fuck!
不是真的 不是真的
This isn't real! It's not real!
It's not real! It's not real!
不是真的 不是真的
没事吗
Is everything all right?
没事 我们结下帐
Yeah, yeah. Could we get the check?
这是潘尼怀斯搞的鬼
That's what Pennywise does, right?
他在整我们 史丹利应该没事
He fucks with us. So, Stanley's probably fine.
迈克 你有他电话吗
Hey, Mike. Do you have Stan's number?
有
Yeah.
嗨 瑞奇
Hey, Richie.
你怎么
How'd you...
你怎么知道我名字
How'd you know my name?
好戏刚刚上演
The fun's just beginning.
对吧
Right?
他说什么
What he said, is it...
你觉得有趣吗
Listen. You think this is funny?
好笑吗
All right?
你觉得这是游戏吗
Think this is some sort of game, huh?
操你妈
Well, fuck you, all right?
瑞奇 注意轻重
Rich, be careful, dude.
操你妈 我不怕你
Fuck you! I'm not afraid of you!
"好戏刚刚上演"
"The fun's just beginning. "
你脱口秀的台词啊 我是你粉丝啊
The line from your act, dude. I'm a fan.
- 那是你家长吗 - 嗯
- Are those your parents? - Yeah.
你想要合照吗
You want a picture?
- 你还好吗 迪恩 - 我不要了
- You okay, Dean? Come on. - I think I'm good.
好吧 很可爱的小孩
Okay, cool. He's a good kid.
天哪 瑞奇 你不记得你自己节目的
Jesus, Richie. You don't remember a line...
台词吗
from your own show?
又不是我自己写的台本
I don't write my own material.
我他妈就知道 我就知道
I fucking knew it! I fucking knew it!
你好 尤瑞斯太太 我是贝弗莉·马什
Hello, Mrs. Uris. My name's Beverly Marsh.
抱歉打扰你了
I apologize for calling,
我是你丈夫的老朋友
but I'm an old friend of your husband's.
你骗了我们 那可不行
You lied to us. That's not okay.
你应该一开始就坦诚告诉我们
Yeah, first words out of your mouth should have been like,
"喂 兄弟 你想回德利镇送死吗"
"Hey, man. You want to come to Derry and get murdered?"
因为这样我就会拒绝
'Cause then I would have said no.
伙计们
Guys.
他妈的圈套
Fucking entrapment, man.
哦
Oh...
他去世了
He passed.
什么时候的事
When did it happen?
昨天
Yesterday.
他走的方式 太可怕了
It was horrible, the way he died.
他的手腕
His wrists.
- 在浴缸 - 在浴缸
- In the bathtub. - In the bathtub.
我很抱歉 我得挂了
I'm sorry. I have to go.
我们很遗憾 帕蒂
We're all very sorry, Patty.
谢谢你
Thank you.
史丹利
Stanley.
潘尼怀斯算到了 在我们之前算到了
Pennywise knew. He knew before we did.
我们要阻止它 我有个计划
We have to stop him. I have a plan.
我有个赶紧逃走的计划
I got a plan. Getting the fuck out of Dodge...
趁着还没到比尔书里的结局那么惨
before this ends worse than one of Bill's books.
谁加入
Who's with me?
我们彼此发过誓的
We made a promise to each other.
那我们一起背弃誓言
Let's un-make the promise.
瑞奇 无辜的人会死
Richie, other people are gonna die.
每天都有人死
Other people die every day, man!
我们又不欠这镇子什么
We don't owe this town shit!
而且我大概两小时前才记起我在这里长大这回事
Plus, I just remembered I grew up here, like, two hours ago.
反正我他妈走了 去他妈的
So, I'm fucking leaving. Fuck this.
抱歉 我同意瑞奇的话
I'm sorry, man, I'm with Richie.
- 小艾 别这样 - 听着
- Eds, please. - Listen.
我们呆在这会死的 对吗
What? We stay, we die, that's it?
我要回旅馆 收拾行李
I'm gonna go back to the inn, I'm gonna pack up my shit,
然后开车回家
and I'm gonna drive to my home.
抱歉兄弟 祝你好运
I'm sorry, man. Good luck.
别走 艾迪 拜托了 艾迪
No, Eddie. Please. Please, Eddie!
等等 艾迪
Eddie, wait!
你还好吗
You okay?
我跟他们回去
I'm gonna head back to the Town House, too.
- 你一起吗 - 好的
- Are you coming? - Yeah.
你应该坦诚的 迈克
You should have told us, Mikey.
比尔 拜托了
Bill. Please, man.
我求你了 兄弟
I'm begging you. Please.
请你听我说
Just listen to me, man. Please.
你要说什么
What are you gonna say?
你还能说什么
What could you possibly say...
能改变现状吗
that would make any kind of a difference?
他们都走了
They're all gone.
我给你看样东西
Come on. Let me show you something.
就一样 你想走的话 随时可以走
One thing. And if you want to leave, you can leave.
但是你先看看 拜托了
Just let me show you this first. Please.
"一圈歪" 什么破名字啊
Lapskew! What kind of name is that, huh?
我妈妈都打得比你好
My mom swings better than you!
你要我说多少遍啊
How many times do I have to...
她不会打棒球都比你们强 垃圾
She doesn't even play baseball! You suck!
妈妈 还要多久
Mommy, how much longer?
维多利亚 我们来看比赛
Victoria, we came to watch the game.
就好好看比赛
We're gonna watch the game.
你好小维
Hello, Vicky.
你朋友也这样叫你吧 小维
Isn't that what your friends call you?
小维
Vicky?
我是怎么知道的
How did I know that?
说明我也是你的朋友
I guess I must be your friend, too.
你要是我的朋友 为什么躲在黑暗里
If you're my friend, why are you hiding in the dark?
你不是我的朋友 你很吓人
You're not my friend. You're scary.
你哭什么
Why are you crying?
人们总是因为我的外貌取笑我
People always make fun 'cause of the way I look.
我想你要是看不见我的脸
I thought if you couldn't see my face,
也许愿意跟我做朋友
then maybe you'd want to be my friend.
算了吧
Never mind.
又老又蠢的潘尼怀斯 你永远都不会有朋友
Oh, silly old Pennywise, you'll never have no friends.
人们也取笑我
People make fun of me, too.
是吗
They do?
因为这个
Cause of this.
那也太愚蠢了
Well, isn't that silly?
因为那个小东西
That little thing?
我马上就能把它吹走
Why, I can blow that thing right away.
你能吗
You could?
当然
Oh, yes!
轻轻一吹就不见了
One poof and it'd be gone!
但是你得离我很近 近到能看见我的脸才行
You would have to get close enough to see my face.
我不确定了 小维
I don't know, Vicky.
不 没关系 我不会笑你的 我保证
No, it's okay. I won't make fun. I promise.
你保证吗
Promise promise?
好吧好吧
Well, okie-dokie!
来靠近一点
Just come on in a little closer,
然后数到三我就把它吹走
and we'll blow it away on the count of three!
一
One,
二
two...
你应该要数三了
You're supposed to say three.
卧槽
Holy fuck.
哈
Boo!
爽
Fuck yeah!
嘿 霍克斯塔
Hey, Hockstetter.
走
Let's go!
(德利旅馆 无空房)
拿上行李然后我们就走
Let's get our shit and get the fuck out of here.
你把你的行李放这里了吗
Did you leave your stuff here?
没有 还在车里
No, my stuff's still in the car.
- 告诉我 - 告诉你什么
- Tell me. - Tell you what?
你此刻在害怕的东西
Whatever it is you're afraid to tell me right now.
小贝
Bev. Bev.
刚才在酒店 你在和史丹利的妻子打电话的时候
Back at the Jade when you were on the phone with Stanley's...
别说了
Stop.
她告诉你她在浴缸里发现他
She told you that she found him in the bathtub,
但是 小贝 我看到你
but, Bev, I saw you.
我听到了 是你先说的
I heard it. You said it first.
不管你们在说什么
Whatever you guys are talking about,
快点说完 我们要走了
let's make it happen faster, all right? We gotta go.
爱德华多 安德雷 我们走吧
Eduardo, andale! Let's go!
你有事没告诉我们
There's something you're not telling us.
你早就知道史丹利是怎么死的 你知道
You knew how Stanley died. You knew.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
我不能说
I can't do this.
她早就知道史丹利会死
She knew how Stanley was going to die,
她是这么跟你说的吗
is that what she just said?
你不能就这么避而不谈
You can't just walk away from this.
你是怎么知道他是在哪里自杀的
How did you know where he killed himself?
小贝
Bev.
跟我聊聊
Talk to me.
跟我聊聊 像从前一样
Just talk to me. Like we used to.
拜托 你是怎么知道的
Come on, how did you know?
因为我看见了
Because I saw it.
我看见我们都死了
I've seen all of us die.
我刚拿了我的盥洗用品
Okay, I just got to grab my toiletry bag,
我们可以走了
and then we can go.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
那个图书馆
The library?
这个地方以前是不是更大
Didn't this place used to be bigger?
迈克 你要去哪
Yo! Mike, where are you going?
迈克 你住在这里吗
Mike, you live here?
是的 别客气
Yeah. Make yourself at home.
- 你要水吗 - 好的
- You want some water? - Yeah, sure.
记忆就是关键
You see, memory's the thing.
是关键
It's the key.
是一切的关键
It's the key to everything.
如果它真的想要我们回到这里
If It really does want us back here,
你不觉得最好的选择
don't you think the smartest thing we can do...
就是离开德利吗
is just get the hell out of Derry?
不不不 它确实想要我们回来
No, no, no. It does want us back.
它当然想了
Of course It does!
但是它不知道我知道什么
But It doesn't know I know what I know.
你知道什么
What do you know?
怎么杀死它
How to kill the shit out of It!
每本书我都读了
I've read every book.
也和这个堕落之镇的所有人都交谈过
I've talked to every person in this godforsaken town,
所有愿意和我谈的人
everybody that would talk to me, anyway,
虽然人数不多
and that's not a long list.
但是还不够
But it wasn't enough.
我不知道这一切是如何开始的
I had to know how this all started.
它是如何开始的
How It started.
它开始于
And It started...
- 这里 - 喔噢
- here. - Whoa.
- 这是什么 迈克 - 这是个手工艺品
- What am I looking at, Mike? - It's an artifact.
来自十八世纪早期的沙科皮族
Early 18th century Shokopiwah.
沙科…你从哪弄来的
Shoko... How'd you get it?
我找到的 在…
I found it, in the...
不是 他们给我的
No, no, they gave it to me.
我偷的
I stole it.
你偷的
You stole it?
从印第安人那里
From Native Americans?
- 这很复杂 - 确实
- It's complicated. - Yeah, it is.
他们在我旅行的时候帮助了我
They helped me on my journey.
这太美了
So beautiful.
他们给我看了一些东西 一幅景象
They showed me things. A vision.
卧槽
Holy fuck.
我感觉很奇怪
I feel kind of funky.
很热
Hot.
我出汗了吗
Am I sweating?
我需要你看他们让我看到的景象 比尔
I need you to see what they showed me, Bill.
比尔
Bill.
他们生活在德利镇之外
They live outside of Derry.
它的势力范围之外
Beyond It's reach.
他们是很多年前搬走的
They moved there many years ago.
他们是圣人
Their holy man,
最虔诚的圣人
their holy of holies,
他们接纳了我
he took me in.
给我喝他们神圣的马图林
Fed me their sacred Maturin.
我开始 有了反应
I started to... to react.
所有生物必须遵循
All living things must abide by the laws...
自身肉体外形的法则
of the shape they inhabit.
当我坐在那里朝山谷外看的时候
While I sat there, looking out over the valley,
我看见它来了
I saw It arrive.
我知道有一天 我会让你们所有人都看见
I knew that one day, I would have to make you all see.
迈克
Mike,
你在我的水里下药了吗
did you put something in my drink?
那是
It's, uh...
植物根茎
It's a root.
你 你给我下药
You... You drugged me?
- 你给我下药 - 不 那是具有效力的植物根茎
- You drugged me? - No, it's a root with properties.
那只是沙科皮人给我的一小剂量
It's just a micro-dose of what the Shokopiwah gave me...
你为什么要怎么做
Why would you do that?
为了张开你的眼睛
To open my eyes.
我感觉不太好
I don't feel real good.
我要你 看
I need you to look,
然后你就会看见
and you'll see.
我感觉不太好
I don't feel good.
睁开眼
Open your eyes.
他们让我看见了过去
They showed me the past.
让我看见它是如何显现在他们面前的
Showed me the way It appeared to them.
让我看见了他们的痛苦
They showed me their pain.
让我看见了如何阻止它
They showed me how to stop It!
结束了
It's over.
结束了 你还好吗
It's over. You're okay.
没事吧 你看见了吗
You're okay. Did you see it?
那个仪式
The ritual?
- 那个丘德仪式 - 我就知道
- The Ritual of Chud? - Yeah, I knew you...
你会看见的
I knew you would see it.
迈克 一切我都看见了
I saw the whole fucking thing, Mike.
那就是我们杀死它的办法
That's how we kill It.
我们要怎么做
How are we going to do it?
其他人都拒绝了
Everybody already said no.
你说
But with you,
他们就会听
they'll listen.
我们一起 就会成功
This won't work without all of us.
好吧 你说看见我们都死了是什么意思
Okay. So, what do you mean that you've seen us all die?
是的 我必须说实话
Yeah, 'cause I gotta be honest.
这只是偶然发生的糟心事罢了
That's a fucked-up thing to just drop on somebody.
自从我离开了德利
Every night since Derry,
我都在做噩梦
I've been having these nightmares.
痛苦的人们 渐渐死去的人们
People in pain. People dying.
人们
People...
好吧 你做噩梦
So, you have nightmares.
我做噩梦 所有人都会做噩梦
I have nightmares. People, they have nightmares.
但是这不意味着你看见的都是真的
But that doesn't mean that your visions are true.
这周我看见了我们每一个人
I've watched every single one of us...
你看见我们每个人 怎么了
You've seen every single one of us what?
去到了史丹利死的地方
At the place that Stanley wound up.
那就是我们的结局
That's how we end.
那我们其他人怎么没看到
Okay, how come the rest of us aren't seeing that shit?
凭什么她看到的就是真的
I mean, what makes her so different?
死亡之光
The Deadlights.
她是我们中唯一一个
She was the only one of us...
在那天被死亡之光照射到的人
that got caught in the Deadlights that day.
我们都被它触碰到了
We were all touched by It.
被改变
Changed.
在我们内心深处 就像被病毒感染了
Deep down. Like an infection. Or a virus.
病毒 你懂吗
A virus. You understand.
慢慢地…
Slowly growing.
生长了27年的病毒
That virus, it's been growing for 27 years.
一直以来 都在生长着
This whole time, metastasizing.
只是它先打倒了史丹 因为
It just got to Stan first, because...
他是最弱的
He was the weakest.
老天啊 瑞奇
Jesus Christ, Rich.
我只是把每个人心里的想法说出来而已
Just saying what everyone else is thinking, man.
瑞奇 别这样
I mean, Rich, come on.
贝弗莉所看见的事 都会实现
What Beverly sees, it will come to pass.
除非我们阻止它
It's what'll happen to all of us, eventually,
否则它就会发生
unless we stop It.
我们要怎么阻止
How the hell are we supposed to do that?
丘德仪式
The Ritual of Chud.
沙科皮族人
The Shokopiwah.
第一批对抗它的人 他们有一句谚语
The first ones who fought It, they have a saying.
"所有生物都必须遵循
"All living things must abide by...
自身肉体外形的法则"
The laws of the shape they inhabit. "
部落仪式
A tribal ritual?
你他妈在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
一定还有其他的办法
All right, there's gotta be another way.
这个东西每隔27年就会回来吗
Okay? This thing comes back, what, every 27 years?
我们不如使用缓兵之计 以后再说吧
Let's just kick the can down the road and do it then.
到那时候我们就70岁了 混蛋
Wait, we'll be 70 years old, asshole.
那样行不通的
It doesn't work that way.
我们活不到下一个20年了
None of us make it another 20 years,
我们都逃不掉
and the way it happens...
所以 如果我们这次不打败它
So, if we don't beat It this cycle, then...
我们会死
We die.
恐怖地死
Horribly.
我不想要恐怖的死法
Yeah, I don't need the "Horribly" Part.
我可没说 是她说的 不是我
I didn't say it. She said it. Not me.
好了 伙计们
All right, guys. Look.
我看见了他所说的事情
I've seen what he's talking about,
全都是真的
and it's all true.
那是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
如果我们想要这个仪式成功
If we want this ritual to work...
我们就要找回记忆
We have to remember.
什么记忆
Remember what?
(寻人启事)
如果让你们都看过的话会更好
It's better if I show you.
但是我们没有时间了
We don't have much time.
这次循环马上就要结束了
His cycle will end soon.
(德利日报 荒地惊现人体残肢)
一旦结束了
And once it does...
我们就完了
We're fucked.
荒地
The Barrens.
这是那次石头大战后
This is where we came.
我们来的地方
After the rock fight.
俱乐部之屋
The clubhouse.
- 你给我们造的 - 是啊
- You built that for us. - Yeah,
那个门板一定就在这附近
the hatch has got to be around here someplace.
就是你做的 我还记得
You did. I do remember that!
- 哦 - 喔噢 喔噢
- Oh! - Whoa! Whoa!
你还好吗
You okay?
- 什么 - 没什么 就是
- What? - Nothing, it's just...
你一点都没变呢
You haven't changed.
挺好的
It's a good thing.
我觉得那个门好像就在
You know what? I actually think the door was more like...
这附近
around...
找到了
Found it.
我没事
I'm okay!
快下来
Come down!
这是什么鬼地方
What the dick is this?
你怎么建的
How'd you build it?
你什么时候建的
When did you build it?
偶尔有空的时候吧
Here and there, I guess.
我之前就挖好了
It was already dug out from something,
只剩下墙壁还需要加固一下
so I just had to reinforce the walls and...
然后再搞一点木头来做门
get some wood for the roof door and...
就差不多了
that's pretty much it.
就我的第一次来说 还不错吧
Pretty good for my first time, huh?
那个特点太酷了
Now, that's a cool feature.
你把手放到另一根柱子上
What happens when you put your hand...
会发生什么 教授
on the other pillar, professor?
现在你们知道 为什么这里会有安全规范
Okay, you see, this is exactly why there are safety codes,
我们需要准许了吧
why we have permits.
这个地方太危险了 你明白吗
This place is a death trap. You understand that?
这是个还未完工的项目 艾迪
Well, it's a work in progress. Okay, Eddie?
话说在前头 如果我受伤了 你要负责
Just so you know, I get hurt, you are liable.
这是什么 这个铁娘子里的开关
And, also, what is this? The switch of an iron maiden?
那是个手电筒
That's a flashlight.
那又是啥 马栓吗
What is that, a horse hitch?
你什么时候把马带下来
When do you have horses down...
这太酷了
Oh, this is cool.
那个东西三美元呢
That was like, three dollars,
拜托你小心点
so be careful with that, please.
我有一个这个 嘿 史丹 你看见了吗
I have one of these. Hey, Stan, you see this?
看见了 你能不要…
Yeah, okay, can you maybe not?
不要哪样 是哦是哦 等等 不要哪样
Maybe not what? Yeah, yeah, hold on. Maybe not what?
耍帅 找乐子
Be awesome and have fun...
享受波板球的魔力
and celebrate the magic of the paddle-ball?
干得好 蠢蛋 你把它弄坏了
Oh, good going, fucknut. You broke his thing.
- 我弄坏了 - 没错
- I broke it? - Yeah,
你把它弄坏了 用你的脸
you broke it with your face.
什么
What?
我才不会把手伸进那种地方呢
I'm not putting my fucking hand down there.
老兄 太酷了
Oh, man. That's so cool.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我们怎么都不记得来过这了
How do we all not remember that this was here?
嘿 废柴们
Hey, Losers.
漂浮吧
Time to float.
- 哈 - 你大爷的 瑞奇
- Ahh! - Fuck, Richie.
- 老兄 - 还记得它以前挂在嘴边的话吗
- Dude! - Remember when he used to say that shit?
他还会跳着小舞
And he'd do that little dance.
只有我一个人记得这些吗
Am I the only one who remembers this shit?
我们在老家期间你要一直表现得这么怪异吗
Are you gonna be like this the entire time we're home?
行吧 我只是想调节一下气氛
All right. Just trying to add some levity to this shit.
我哪凉快哪呆着去了
I'll go fuck myself.
这里味道太臭了
It smells so fucking terrible in here.
(废柴专用 史丹)
嘿 大家
Hey, you guys?
这个写着"史丹"
This says "Stan. "
"废柴专用"
"For the use of Losers only. "
比尔
Bill.
这他妈是什么
The fuck is this?
可以让我们在这里的时候
So you don't get spiders stuck...
不让蜘蛛爬到头发里
in your hair when you're down here.
史丹利 我们才不怕蜘蛛
Stanley, we're not afraid of fucking spiders.
我坚守立场
I stand corrected.
这可是头一回
That's a first.
确实
Touche.
嘿 瑞奇 你的十分钟到了
Hey, Rich, your ten minutes are up.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
说好了每人只能用吊床十分钟
The hammock. Ten minutes each was the rule.
我可没看见任何告示
I don't see any sign.
你又开始这样了是吗 不不不
Are you being this way right now? Really? No, no, no.
如果大家都同意了 为什么会没有告示呢
Why would there be a sign if it was a verbal agreement?
我不记得你们都同意了那个规矩
And I remember you agreeing on the fucking rule!
- 你小妹妹露出来了 - 每个人十分钟
- I can see your vagina! - Ten minutes each.
滚回你的小角落去
Go back in your dumb little corner!
我操了你妈
I fucked your mom!
放屁 你给我把那句话收回去
No, you didn't. Take that back!
新来的 你还真擅长这个
You're awfully good at this, new kid.
你真这么觉得吗
You really think so?
港口那里有个暑期课程
There's actually a summer program in Bar Harbor.
教你一些建筑学的知识
Teaches you, like, everything about architecture.
我一直想申请来着
I was thinking about applying.
我会报名
I'll do that.
我会想方设法离开德利
I'll do anything to get the hell out of Derry.
等我毕业了 我要去佛罗里达州
Man, when I graduate, I'm going to Florida.
去佛罗里达干嘛 迈克
What's in Florida, Mike?
我不知道
I don't know.
我只是一直想去那里
You know, I guess it's just a place I always wanted to go.
史丹 你应该和迈克一起去佛罗里达
Stan, you should go with Mike to Florida.
你已经像个80岁的老头了
You already act 80.
你会很受老奶奶喜欢的
You'd clean up with all the grandmas.
你们觉得我们还会是朋友吗
Do you guys think we'll still be friends?
等我们长大之后
When we're older?
什么
What?
为什么不会呢
Why wouldn't we be?
你们的父母现在
Do any of your parents still hang out...
还和他们中学时期的朋友玩吗
with their friends from middle school?
我是说 事情是会变的
I mean, things might be different then.
我们都会变的
We all might be different.
我们永远都会是朋友的 我知道
We'll always still be friends. I know.
我不觉得
I don't think that just...
那会因为我们长大而改变
goes away because we get older.
对啊 史丹 别这么说
Yeah, Stan. Come on.
你不用表现得这么
You don't have to be so...
悲伤
Sad.
他一直都很早熟
He was old before his time.
是啊
Yeah.
真好奇他长大了是什么样的
I wonder what he was like all grown up.
也许和他小时候一样
Probably what he was like as a kid.
最好的样子
The best.
给
Here.
好吧 迈克 我们在这里干嘛
All right, Mike. What are we doing here?
那个仪式
The ritual.
要进行仪式 需要献祭
To perform it requires a sacrifice.
- 我建议献祭艾迪 - 等等 什么
- Sacrifice? I nominate Eddie. - Wait, what?
因为你身材最小 放得上烤架
Because you're little. You'll fit on a barbeque.
我身高1米79 这可是世界平均水平
I'm 5'9". It's, like, average height in most of the world.
不是那种献祭 大伙
It's not that kind of a sacrifice, guys.
迈克
Mike?
过去被埋葬了
The past is buried.
但是你们要去把过去挖出来
But you're gonna have to dig it up.
一点一点地
Piece by piece.
而那些片段
And these pieces,
那些信物
these artifacts,
就是我们回来的意义
that's why we're here.
就是你们的献祭品
They are what you'll sacrifice.
而既然史丹不在这里 无法挖掘过去
And since Stan isn't here to find his...
我觉得我们要一起去
I figured we should all be here together...
找他的信物
to find his artifact.
我觉得比尔已经找到了
I think Bill just did that.
好的 迈克 所以我们要去哪里找我们的信物
Okay, Mike, so where do we find our tokens?
我必须说实话 恕我直言
Yeah, I gotta be honest, man. All due respect.
这太蠢了 好吗
This is fucking stupid, all right?
我们为什么需要信物
Why do we need tokens? All right?
我们已经记起来所有事了
We already remember everything.
我们救了小贝 打败了它
Saving Bev, defeating It...
我们已经想起来了
I mean, we're caught up!
这还不是全部
It's not everything.
我们打了一架 那之后发生了什么
We fought. But what happened after that?
在内尔波特的房子前面
Before the house on Neibolt.
想一想
Think.
我们记不起来了 对吗
We can't remember, can we?
我们的故事还有遗漏
See, there's more to our story.
那个夏天发生的事情
What happened that summer.
那些记忆的空白
And those blank spaces,
像从书上撕掉的书页
like pages torn out of a book.
那就是你们要寻找的
That's what you need to find.
我们需要分开行动
We need to split up.
你们每个人都要找到你们的信物
You each need to find your artifact.
单独去 这很重要
Alone. That's important.
当你们找到之后
When you do,
今晚来图书馆找我
meet me at the library tonight.
我不得不说
Yeah, I gotta say,
从数据上来看 如果是求生场景
statistically speaking, you look at survival scenarios,
我们一起行动的存活率更高
we're gonna do much better as a group.
是啊 分头行动太傻了
Yeah, splitting up would be dumb, man.
我们要一起去 好吗
Okay, we gotta go together. All right?
我们那个夏天就是一起的 对吗
We were together that summer, right?
不对
No.
不是一直都在一起
Not that whole summer.
收回你的话
Take it back.
比尔
Bill!
你们就是一群懦夫
You're just a bunch of losers.
滚开
Fuck off!
- 操 - 停下
- Fucking... - Stop!
我们是一起弄伤它的
We were all together when we hurt It.
所以我们都还活着
That's why we're still alive.
是吗 好吧 那我还想多活几年
Yeah? Well, I plan to keep it that way.
我打赌明天
I bet by tomorrow,
我们又会团结在一起
we'll all be back together.
我不觉得
I don't think so.
如果我们要打败它 就必须这么做
Well, if we're gonna stop It, we better be.
也许瑞奇是对的
Maybe Richie was right.
也许我们什么都不用做 也许我们什么也做不了
Maybe we shouldn't do anything about It, or maybe we can't.
别让他们改变你的想法
Okay, don't let them get to you.
现在这么说有点迟了
It's a little late for that.
我要走了
You should go.
免得你爸爸看见
Before your dad sees.
你好
Yes?
不好意思
Sorry. I...
(克什)
要帮忙吗
May I help you?
我以为这里住的是马什
I thought I rang Marsh.
马什
Marsh?
艾文·马什
Alvin Marsh?
我父亲
My father.
我是在这里长大的
I grew up here.
亲爱的
Dear,
本不应该由我来告诉你这个
it's not for me to tell you this,
但是 你的父亲去世了
but your father passed away.
很抱歉 你不知道吗
I'm so sorry. You didn't know?
我们很久没有联系了
We hadn't spoken in a while.
你为什么不进来呢
Well, won't you come in?
让我给你倒点水喝
Let me offer you something to drink.
不用了 我要走了
No, it's fine. I have to go.
这是我唯一能做的了
It's the least I can do.
好吧
Sure. Okay.
这里和你记忆中的一样吗
Is it like you remember?
更干净了
Cleaner.
你先四处看看
Well, you feel free to look around...
我去烧水
while I get the water boiling.
真的 不用了 你不用麻烦
Oh, really, it's fine. You don't need to do that.
别这么客气
Don't be so polite.
今天是她的生日
Today is her birthday.
我还能闻到她的香水味
I can still smell her perfume.
如果不是因为你 她还活着
And she'd still be alive if it wasn't for you.
妈妈病了
Mama was sick.
你知道她那么做是因为她病了
You know that's why she did what she did.
她那么做
She did what she did...
是因为她为做你的母亲感到羞耻
because she was embarrassed to be your mother.
你长得跟她很像
You look like her.
但是你和她完全没得比
But you are nothing like her.
过来
Come here.
我说给我过来
I said come here!
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
你知道我永远不会伤害你的
You know that I would never hurt you.
你知道的 是吗
You know that, don't you?
对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
你永远都是我的乖女儿 对吗
You'll always be my little girl, won't you?
永远都是
Always.
"卿之秀发如冬焰
"Your hair is winter fire,
初月余烬未绝
January embers...
引吾心燃烧"
My heart burns there, too. "
给你 实在抱歉
There. I do apologize.
每年这个时候都特别热
It gets so very hot here this time of year.
没关系
It's fine.
我感觉自己时日无多了
Well, you feel like you could just about die.
但是你知道人们怎么说德利的
But you know what they say about Derry.
"这里的人从来都没有真正死去过"
"No one who dies here ever really dies. "
告诉我 你回到德利有何感想
But tell me, how is it being back in Derry?
有点怪怪的
It's good. Strange.
怪
Strange?
我的天
Oh, my.
怎么怪了
Strange, how?
你来之前我烤了一些饼干
I had some cookies in the oven before you came.
坐在那别动
You stay right there.
我真的不想再给你添麻烦了
I really... I shouldn't impose... I'm gonna...
不 你一定要尝尝
No, no, no. I insist.
克什夫人 这是你的家人吗
Mrs. Kersh, are these your family?
是的
Yes, dear.
我父亲来到这个国家时口袋里只有14美元
My father came to this country with $14 in his pocket.
但是他并没有接受施舍
And he didn't ask for a handout...
不像现在的人们
the way that people come in here these days.
你知道他做了什么吗
You know what he did?
他做了什么 克什夫
What did he do, Mrs. Kersh?
他加入了马戏团
My father joined the circus.
(跳舞小丑潘尼怀斯)
我一直都是父亲的乖女儿
I was always Daddy's little girl.
你呢
What about you?
你还是爸爸的乖女儿吗 贝弗莉
Are you still his little girl, Beverly?
是吗
Are you?
别对爸爸撒谎
Mustn't lie to our father!
救命
Help!
逃避 你就只会逃避
Run, run, run, run.
真是一点都没变啊
You haven't changed anything yet.
你没有改变他们的未来
You haven't changed their futures.
你更没能拯救他们
You... You haven't saved any of them.
乖乖闭上眼 贝贝
Close your eyes, Bev.
去死吧
Fuck you!
如果你不相信我的话
If you don't believe,
就闭上眼
close them...
看看
and see!
(感谢那些回忆 德利镇)
(出租)
(街头霸王)
(游戏代币)
加油啊 加油
Come on, you. Come on.
肯 你这个小混蛋
Ken, you little bitch...
我赢了
Yes!
- 你真厉害 - 游戏结束
- You're fucking good. - Game over.
我得走了
Ah, well, I gotta go.
要不再来一局
How about we go again?
再玩一会吧
Play some more, you know?
去你妈的
Fuck you, man.
你不想的话就算了
Only if you want to.
哥们 你突然这么肉麻干嘛
Dude, why are you being weird?
我可不是你男朋友
I'm not your fucking boyfriend.
我没
I... I didn't...
你们他妈在干什么
What the fuck's going on here?
你们之前可没跟我说过
You assholes didn't tell me...
这里到处是同性恋
your town is full of little fairies.
李察·妈的·托兹
Richie fucking Tozier?
怎么 你不会是想干我的小表弟吧
What? You're trying to bone my little cousin?
给我滚出去 死基佬
Get the fuck out of here, faggot!
快滚啊
Fucking move!
想要亲亲吗 瑞奇
Want a kiss, Richie?
这些都是幻觉 幻觉 幻觉
It's not real. It's not real. It's not real. It's not real.
我好像吓尿了
I think I just shit my pants.
- 航海节闭幕式今晚举行 - 什么鬼
- Canal Days Festival. Closing performance is tonight. . - Shit.
到时见哦 小帅哥
Hope to see you there, handsome.
(沉痛悼念 李察·托兹)
想我了吗 瑞奇
Did you miss me, Richie?
该死
Oh, fuck!
我可是对你日思夜想呢
'Cause I've missed you.
再也没有人想陪小丑玩了
No one wants to play with the clown anymore.
来和我玩个游戏吧
Play a game with me, would ya?
玩街霸怎么样
How about Street Fighter?
我知道 你超喜欢玩 不是吗
Oh, yes. You like that one, don't you?
不然真心话大冒险也行
Or maybe Truth or Dare?
天呐
Jesus.
你是不想
Oh, you wouldn't want...
让人听到你的真心话吗 瑞奇
anyone to pick "truth," though, would ya, Richie?
你害怕别人发现你的秘密
You wouldn't want anyone to know what you're hiding.
*可我知道你的小秘密*
*I know your secret*
*你那难以启齿的小秘密*
*Your dirty, little secret*
*你的秘密*
*Oh, I know your secret*
*难以启齿的小秘密*
*Your dirty, little secret*
要我和你朋友们说说吗 瑞奇
Should I tell them, Richie?
这些都是幻觉 都是假的
This isn't happening. This isn't real.
都是假的 都是幻觉 不是真的
It isn't real. It isn't happening. It isn't real.
回来玩啊
Come back and play!
快回来陪小丑玩
Come back and play with the clown!
- 我很抱歉 抱歉 - 看着点路 混蛋
- I'm so sorry. Sorry. - Watch it, you jerk!
对不起
Sorry.
(玫瑰二手专卖店)
天啊
Oh, man!
- 有什么需要的吗 - 你好
- Can I help you? - Hi.
我想看看这个…
Yeah, I want to see about the...
棒球卡
Baseball card?
还是保龄球
The bowling ball?
不是 是
No, the...
班卓琴
Banjo?
海狸标本
Beaver?
他妈的自行车
Fucking bike.
你要用这种方式说话的话
You wanna use that kind of language,
那就出去吧
take it out in the street.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们就当什么都没发生过好吗
Can we just start over and pretend that I just walked in?
有什么需要的吗
How can I help you?
谢谢 我想买那辆自行车
Thank you. Yes. I want to buy the bike.
你是威廉·丹柏吗 那个作家
Aren't you William Denbrough, the writer?
没错 就是
Yeah, that's...
就是我
That's me.
那辆自行车本来是我的
That bike used to be mine.
但是它现在归我了
Well, it's mine now.
不过你可是大作家
But you're the big author.
你想买它不是轻而易举
You want it, you can afford it.
行 开个价吧
All right. How much?
三百
$300.
也不多吧
You can afford it.
我给您拿
I'll get it.
我们这算是谈妥了是吧
I guess that's kind of a deal.
(威廉·丹柏 《黑流》)
你 想要个签名吗
You... You want me to sign it for you?
免了 结局不咋地
No, I didn't like the ending.
三百美元
Three big ones.
车是你的了
All yours.
不知道还能跑多快
I don't know how fast she'll go.
放那好多年了
Been there a lot of years.
老人家 你知道吗
You know what, mister?
她曾经可是我的驱魔座驾
She was fast enough to beat the devil.
加把劲 伙计
Come on.
我也很想你
Yeah, I missed you, too.
酷
Yeah!
银翼号 出发
Hi-ho, Silver!
前进
Away!
再见 比利
Bye, Billy!
(杰克逊街)
我知道你就在下面
I know you're down there.
我知道你能听到
I know you can hear me.
我只想知道
There's something I have to know.
镇上明明有这么多孩子
All of the kids in this town you could have taken,
为什么偏偏挑中了小乔
why Georgie?
说话啊
Say something!
为什么偏偏是他
Why him?
为什么 为什么
Why him? Why him? Why him?
为什么
Why?
因为你不在啊 比利
Because you weren't there, Billy.
比利 别走
Billy, don't leave.
有人吗
Hello?
比利
Billy.
我还被困在这
I'm still here.
救我
Help me.
小乔
Georgie.
Georgie?
救救我 比利
Help me, Billy.
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
快要够到你了 加把劲
I've got you, buddy. Come on.
他来了
He's coming.
抓住我的手
Take my hand!
- 我在这 快把手给我 - 比利 求求你 他来了
- I got you. Come on. - Billy, please. He's coming.
- 抓住我的手 - 比利
- Take my hand. - Billy!
快 抓住我的手
Come on, take my hand!
我恨你
I hate you!
I hate you.
你在和谁说话
Who are you talking to?
躲开 躲开
Move, move, move!
Move! Move!
听到下水道的声音了吗 离它远点
You hear voices from that sewer, you stay away from it.
下水道有声音吗
You hear voices from the sewer?
不是
No.
不是 离下水道远点就行了
No. Just stay away from that sewer.
我只在浴缸里听到过怪声
I only hear voices in the tub.
从下水道传来的
You know. From the drain.
什么样的声音
What kind of voices?
小孩子的
Kids.
有时又像是…
And other times, like a...
小丑吗
Like a clown?
听我说 认真听
You listen to me. You listen good.
你必须离开这里
You need to get out of this town.
跟你父母说 随便找个理由
All right? Tell your parents. Make up a reason.
编个谎 我不管你用什么方法
You make up a fucking lie. I don't care what you do.
只要能离开这里就行
Just get out of this town.
永远别再回来了 明白吗
Make them never bring you back. Do you understand?
离开德利镇 别再回来
You leave Derry and you stay out of Derry!
明白吗
Do you understand me?
我要去狂欢节了
I'm supposed to be at the festival.
说你听懂了
Tell me you understand!
我要去狂欢节了
I'm supposed to be at the festival.
我得走了
I gotta go.
一定要小心
Just be careful!
(欢迎德利镇暑期班学生)
快点 赶紧他妈离开这
Come on, let's get the fuck outta here.
醒醒 肥猪
Wake up, fat-ass.
死废物
Fucking loser.
别怕 是我
Easy. It's just me.
你和你的朋友要去哪呢
What are you and your little buddies up to in here?
那些可不是我朋友
Those guys are definitely not my buddies.
我是说你真正的朋友
No, I meant your real friends.
乔伊 乔纳森 唐尼 丹尼
Joey. Jonathan. Donnie. Danny.
你竟然在学校抽烟吗
Are you smoking in school?
这里是我的秘密基地
Secret hideout.
别告诉别人
Don't tell anyone.
你还好吧 新来的
You okay, new kid?
当然 我没事
Yeah, no, I'm fine.
我只是担心
I guess I'm just worried...
那次争论过后我们没办法和好如初
that we're not all gonna be the same after the fight.
只要还能一起玩 谁在乎这些呢
As long as we can still hang out, who cares?
你说真的吗
You really mean that?
当然了 小傻瓜
Well, yeah, of course, dummy.
我们俩
You and me.
天呐
Oh, my God!
我是说朋友那种
I meant as a friend.
你真以为我会喜欢像你这样
You actually thought I could like someone...
又肥又恶心的家伙吗
as fat and gross and disgusting like you?
写多少肉麻情诗也无济于事
No matter how many stupid poems you write.
"卿之秀发如冬焰
"Your hair is winter fire.
初月余烬未绝
January embers.
引吾心燃烧"
My heart burns there, too. "
(肥猪)
(贝弗莉·马什)
那不是贝弗莉
That's not the real Beverly.
贝弗莉不会说那样的话
Beverly would never say anything like that.
她绝不会说那样的话
She'd never say that.
给我你的吻 小胖子
Kiss me, fat boy.
没人想吻死胖子
Oh, nobody wants to kiss the fat boy.
离我远点
Just leave me alone.
一个人
Alone?
你一直都是一个人啊
Oh, you've always been alone.
胡说 我有朋友
That's not true. I have real friends.
比尔 艾迪 迈克 史丹利 瑞奇和贝弗莉
Bill. Eddie. Mike. Stanley. Richie. Beverly.
他们都是我的好朋友
They're my real friends.
像上次那样亲吻我吧
Kiss me as if it were the last time.
你在干什么 小屁孩
What the hell are you doing, kid?
伙计们
Guys?
嗨
Hey.
所以 你看到了什么
So, what did you see out there?
我不想见到的东西
Something I wish I hadn't.
所以怎么办 我们就
So, what, we just...
我们干掉它 然后又忘记一切吗
We kill It, and then we just forget everything again?
希望如此 你呢
I hope so. Don't you?
我不知道
I don't know.
我希望我能留存那些美好的回忆
I guess I want to hold on to the good stuff, you know?
我是说 对于过去
Come on. There must be something from...
你肯定也有不想忘记的事吧
the past that you don't want to forget again.
我记得我被吓得屁滚尿流
I remember being scared shitless.
好冷的笑话
Cold.
我记得你们穿着三角短裤
I remember you guys in your tighty-whities.
行吧 这个就忘了吧
Okay. Please forget that moment.
我还记得
I remember this.
有个男孩给我写了这个
I remember the boy who wrote it for me.
我不太记得他
Not him, so much,
而是他给我的那种感觉
but how he made me feel.
和他的吻
And a kiss.
太模糊了 不过我觉得我们在这待得越久
It's still blurry, but I think the longer we're here,
记忆就能越清晰
the more I can see it.
多看看那个场景
The more I can see that moment.
就能想起更多
The more I can see...
是比尔
Bill.
我觉得
I think.
我也不知道 你还记得
I don't know. Do you remember...
小贝
Bev,
- 让开 让开 - 怎么了
- Move. Move. - What's wrong?
我要离开这鬼地方
I'm leaving.
什么 你不能走
What? You can't leave, man.
分开了 大家都会死
We split, we all die.
那我也要试试 反正早晚都得死
Yeah, I'll take my chances. We're gonna die, anyway.
瑞奇
Rich.
海狸宝宝祝你早上好
Hey, kids! It's Burrow the Beaver!
大家快来哦
Come on down.
今天是航海节的最后一天了
It's the last day of the festival here at Canal Days.
混蛋
Asshole!
有人吗
Hello?
您需要什么
Can I help you?
我打了电话
Yeah, I called in...
我有个给卡斯布拉克的处方药
I had prescription called in for Kaspbrak.
卡斯布拉克
Kaspbrak?
吸入器
It's an inhaler.
是艾德华·卡斯布拉克吗
Eddie Kaspbrak?
是我
That's me.
我记得你
I remember you.
嗯
Yeah.
你妈妈近来还好吧
How's your mom?
她几年前就去世了
Well, she died a few years ago.
很不幸 是死于肝癌
It's very sad. It was from liver cancer.
这是什么
What's that?
- 你说什么 - 这个
- What's what? - That.
行了
All right.
别挤了
Okay.
挤不出来 这是个痣
No, it's not gonna pop. It's a mole.
应该不是肿瘤
It might not be cancer.
肿瘤
Cancer?
也可能是
But it might be.
在这等我一下
You just stay here.
我去给你拿点东西
I'll get you something.
好吧
Okay.
又来拿治口臭的药了
You came here for your stinky breath pills?
我没口臭
My breath is fine.
谢谢你的关心
Thank you.
我爸爸可不是这么说的
That's not what my dad said.
他说你的小弟弟上
He said you have a tumor.
长了个肿瘤
On your dick.
谁会因为那个吃药啊
But you don't take pills for...
等等 你爸爸说什么
Wait, what did your dad say?
给你
There you go.
希望这药能让你的小弟弟好受一些
I hope your dick feels better.
多谢了
Thank you.
谢谢你的吸入器 不是指我的那啥
For the inhaler, not for the penis thing.
艾迪
Eddie!
小迪宝贝
Eddie bear!
妈
Mommy?
小迪宝贝
Eddie bear!
妈妈
Mommy?
艾迪 快来救救我
Eddie, come help me! Quick!
艾迪
Eddie!
妈妈
Mommy?
艾迪
Eddie?
艾迪 救我
Eddie, help me!
快点 救我
Quick, help me!
妈妈
Mommy?
小迪 快来救我
Eddie bear, come help me, quick!
艾迪
Eddie?
她怎么会在这
The fuck is she doing here?
你怎么这么磨蹭
What is taking you so long?
我不知道 你怎么在这
I don't know. Why are you here?
妈妈
Mommy!
他要来了 快带我离开这
He's coming! You gotta get me outta here!
- 谁要来了 - 艾迪
- Who's coming? - Eddie.
这他妈是什么
What the fuck is that?
- 妈妈 - 快带我离开这
- Mommy. - You gotta get me outta here.
他来了
He's coming!
他会杀了我的 艾迪
He's gonna kill me! Eddie!
求你了艾迪 救救我 他要感染我
Help! Please, help me! He's going to infect me!
艾迪 他要感染我 艾迪
Eddie! He's gonna infect me! Eddie!
救救我
Help me!
救我艾迪 他来了 艾迪
Help me, Eddie! He's coming, Eddie!
艾迪 快点
Eddie, hurry!
他要感染我 艾迪
He's gonna infect me, Eddie!
天呐 艾迪
Oh, my God! Eddie!
快点 艾迪
Hurry up, Eddie!
艾迪
Eddie!
- 解不开 - 艾迪 艾迪
- I can't do it! - Eddie! Eddie!
抱歉 我解不开
I'm sorry, I can't do it.
你不会丢下我的 艾迪
I knew you wouldn't leave me, Eddie!
艾迪 救救我
Eddie, help me!
艾迪
Eddie!
这些东西怎么还在这
What's all this shit doing here?
这帘子为什么还在
Why is that curtain still here?
好吧 没事的
Okay, all right.
你确定要这样做吗 小艾
Are you gonna do this, Eds?
只是回忆而已
It's just a memory.
只是回忆 没事的
It's just a memory. You're fine.
深呼吸 深呼吸
Deep breath. Deep breath.
好吧 你确定吗
Okay. You gonna do it?
操 他妈的
Shit! Oh, shit! Oh, fuck!
住手
Stop! Stop!
满意了吧
That's right!
去死吧
Fuck you!
发生了什么
What the fuck?
什么
What?
推门 不是拉
Push. Not pulling one.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
我的天 你怎么了
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
没事 我很好
Nothing. I'm fine.
我很好 无事发生
I'm fine. Everything's fine.
你还好吗 其他人呢
Hey, how you doing? Where's everybody else?
瑞奇要走
Richie wants to leave.
本在楼上劝他留下
Ben's upstairs trying to get him to stay.
艾迪被吓到了
Eddie's just scared.
我也害怕 比尔
So am I, Bill.
你不害怕吗
Aren't you?
我们都很害怕
We're all scared.
我担心的就是这一点
That's what worries me.
它就是想让我们害怕
Because that's what It wants.
只要我们团结一致
We can do this,
就能战胜它
but we have to stick together.
我们不应该跑吗
Should we be running?
这里可是德利镇 我都开始习惯了
This is Derry. I'm kinda getting used to it.
(你也没能保护他哦)
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
该死 是那个孩子
Shit. It's the kid.
什么
What?
我们在那个地方见到的孩子
It's the kid from the place.
在中餐厅
The Chinese place.
我在来这的路上遇见他了
I saw him on the way here.
他住在我以前的房子里
He lives at my old house.
他要去狂欢节 而且
He was going to the fair, and...
他要去狂欢节 我得去救他
He's going to the fair. I gotta help him.
等等 等等 听我说 我们一起去
Okay, okay. Listen to me. We'll go together.
我去叫瑞奇和本 然后就出发
I'm gonna get Richie and Ben and we'll go.
没时间了 我不能再让旧事重演
There's no time. I can't let it happen again.
之前的事并不是你的错
What happened before wasn't your fault.
都不是你的错
None of it was.
我也希望是这样 小贝
I wish that were true, Bev.
比尔 小贝
Bill! Bev!
怎么回事 怎么了
What is this? What happened?
比尔怎么就走了
Did Bill just leave?
我拦不住他
I couldn't stop him.
大家都要走
Everybody's leaving.
没关系 相信比尔 他会回来的
It's all right. It's Bill. He'll be back.
他会回来的
He'll come back.
不过还好 瑞奇回心转意了
Well, at least I got Richie to stay.
操
Fuck. Oh.
那该死的麻风病怪 吐了我一身
Oh. And then the leper, he threw up all over me.
"我是迈克·韩洛
"Hey, it's Mike Hanlon.
你们怎么没回缅因州"
Why don't you come back to Maine?"
轮到你了 艾迪
It's your time, Eddie.
搞什么
What?
为什么
Why?
你为什么要这么做
Why did you do that?
因为他说到你了
Because he says it's your time.
谁说的
Who says it's my time?
你知道是谁 艾迪
You know, Eddie.
你知道的
You know.
飘起来吧
Time to float.
你往哪躲呢
Where did he go?
把刀还给老子
Now give me back my fucking knife!
你这发型也该理理了
You should cut that fucking mullet.
看起来像30年没剪过一样
It's been, like, 30 years, man.
伙计们
Guys!
糟糕
Oh, shit.
小艾
Eds.
天呐 小艾 这是怎么回事
Jesus, Eds. What the hell?
- 鲍尔斯在我房里 - 天呐
- Bowers is in my room. - Oh, my...
- 伤得很重吗 - 没有
- Is it bad? - No.
我要把我的名字刻在
I'm gonna carve my whole name...
这死肥猪的肚子上
onto this cottage cheese!
干掉一个
One down!
真他妈爽
Fuck yeah!
(德利镇狂欢节)
等等
Hey!
等等 小鬼 小鬼
Hey, kid! Kid!
抱歉 抱歉
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
等等
Hey!
不好意思 等等
Excuse me. Excuse me. Hey! Hey!
该死
Fuck.
操
Fuck!
小鬼 小鬼
Kid! Hey, kid!
操
Fuck.
小鬼
Kid?
操
Fuck.
小鬼
Kid?
Kid.
小鬼 等等
Kid? Hey! Hey!
小鬼
Kid!
操
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我是来帮你的
No, I'm here to help.
别再跟着我了
Stop following me!
我是来救你出去的
I'm gonna get you out of here.
不
No.
求你
Please.
这次我来了 要抓就抓我吧
I'm here this time. Just take me.
混蛋
Son of a bitch!
救命
Help!
我应该回去
I should go back there.
我就这么置他们于不顾 我应该回去
I just fucking left them in the lurch, man. I should go back there.
你他妈说什么呢 去他妈的
What the fuck are you talking about? Fuck that.
去他们的
Fuck them.
我还要去里诺约会呢
I got dates in fucking Reno, man.
(史丹利·尤瑞斯)
在我刚刚读到的句子中
Reflecting on the meaning of what I just read,
多次提到"升华"二字
the word "Leshanot" comes up a lot,
也就是"改变和转变"
which means "To change, to transform. "
我觉得很符合今天的主题
Which makes sense, I guess,
因为即日起我就要真正成人了
because today I'm supposed to become a man.
其实挺有意思
It's funny, though.
我觉得每个人都有令自己骄傲的回忆 对吗
Everyone I think has the memories they're prouder of than others, right?
或许这就是为什么我们害怕改变
And maybe that's why change is so scary.
因为那些我们想忘却的事
'Cause the things we wish we could leave behind...
- 早上好啊 迈克 - 你好吗
- Good morning, Mike. - How you doing?
那些我们想平息的流言
The whispers we wish we could silence...
他爸爸就是那个纵火犯
His pa is the one. The one that set that fire.
那些我们想摆脱的噩梦
The nightmares we most want to wake up from,
那些我们想改变的记忆
the memories we wish we could change...
那些我们自以为要守住的秘密
the secrets we feel like we have to keep...
都难以摆脱
are the hardest to walk away from.
而美好的记忆呢
The good stuff?
总是我们脑海中最快消逝的画面
The pictures in our mind that fade away the fastest?
总是我们觉得最容易失去的自我碎片
Those pieces of you it feels the easiest to lose.
也许我并不愿忘记
Maybe I don't want to forget.
也许今天的主题就是关于忘记 对吗
Maybe if that's what today is all about, forget it, right?
谢谢 史丹利
Thank you, Stanley.
今天我就要成人了
Today, I'm supposed to become a man,
但我不觉得有什么不一样
but I don't feel any different.
我知道我是个废柴
I know I'm a loser.
不管将来怎样
And no matter what,
我都他妈不会改变
I always fucking will be.
史丹利 谢谢你的出现
Thanks for showing up, Stanley.
(德利镇先驱报 两名毒瘾者在哈里森街大火中死亡)
迈克 救命
Mike! Help!
救命啊
Help us!
- 小迈 求你了 救命啊 - 救命啊
- Please, Mikey, get help! - Help us!
小迈 救命啊
Please, Mikey, get help!
小迈
Mikey!
迈克 你早该被烧死
You should have burned, Mike.
跟你吸毒的爹妈一起
Just like your druggie parents.
你看见他们了吗
Can you see them yet?
像炸鸡一样
Crisping?
被烤得又酥又脆
Like fried fucking...
你应该说 早就该这么干了
I guess you could say that was long overdue.
懂没 因为是在图书馆
Get it? 'Cause we're in a library.
不
No.
迈克
Mike?
- 嘿 - 嘿 我的天啊
- Hey. - Hey. Oh, my God.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
我很不好 我他妈刚杀了个人
No, I'm not all right. I just fucking killed a guy.
我是在问迈克
I was talking to Mike.
比尔在哪
Where's Bill?
比尔 我们在图书馆
Bill, we're all at the library.
你在哪
Where are you at?
它杀了那个孩子 迈克
He took a little kid, Mike.
它把那个孩子杀了 就在我面前
He took a little kid right in fucking front of me.
别别别 听着 反正
No, no, no, no, no. Just, just...
你先来图书馆再说
Look, just come here to the library.
我们可以想一个计划
We can talk about the plan.
- 我要杀了它 - 别这样
- I'm gonna go kill It. - No, no, no.
我不想你们跟我一起被弄死
I don't want any of you to get killed with me.
比尔
Bill! Bill!
他要单独行动了
He's going to fight It alone.
- 什么 - 一个人
- What? - Alone.
关键是大家在一起
It's about the group.
大家不在一起 仪式就起不了作用
The ritual doesn't work without the group.
只有我们一起才有用
Doing it together is why it'd work.
迈克 他有没有说要去哪
Mike, did he tell you where he was going?
他要是想杀掉潘尼怀斯
If he really wanted to kill Pennywise,
那只能去一个地方
there's only one place he'll go.
仪式也必须在那里进行
The same place the ritual needs to be performed.
接下来有的受了 对不对
Oh, we're not gonna like this, are we?
操
Fuck.
比尔
Bill!
不 你们别来
No, no, you guys, no!
一切因我而起
I started all this.
你们在这都是因为我的错
It's my fault that you're all here.
这个纠缠着你们每个人的 该死的诅咒
This curse, this fucking thing that's inside you all.
都是源于那天
It started growing the day...
我拉着你们去了荒地
that I made you go down to the Barrens...
只因我当时只顾着找小乔
because all I cared about was finding Georgie.
现在 我要进去了
Now, I'm gonna go in there,
我也不知道会发生什么
and I don't know what's gonna happen,
但我不能也要你们这么做
but I can't ask you to do this.
不过
Well,
我们也没打算要你同意
we're not asking you, either.
- 小贝 - 既然当时我们都在一起
- Bev... - We didn't do it alone then, Bill,
现在也不会让你独自面对
so we're not gonna do this alone now.
废柴永不分离
Losers stick together.
谁还有话要说吗
So, does somebody want to say something?
上次来的时候瑞奇说的话就很帅
Richie said it best when we were here last.
是吗
I did?
- "我不想死" - 不是
- "I don't want to die"? - Not that.
"没比鸡儿算你走运"
"You're lucky we're not measuring dicks"?
不是
No.
"干死这个垃圾小丑"
"Let's kill this fucking clown"?
Let's kill this fucking clown.
它把这地方改造得还挺讨喜的
Well, I love what he's done with the place.
瑞奇 小心点
Beep-beep, Richie.
好的
All right.
嘿 那是地下室 对不对
Hey, hey. That's the basement, right?
本
Ben?
该死的 别啊 本
No, no! Hey, hey! Ben!
本
Ben!
本 怎么回事
Ben? What's wrong?
- 本 - 好了 好了
- Ben! - Okay. All right.
本
Ben!
这可不妙啊 是吧
Okay, that can't be good, right?
救命
Help! Hey!
是史丹
It's Stan.
(回家)
这不是真的
It can't be real.
天啊
Oh, God.
卧槽
Shit.
要不是你 比尔 我还活得好好的
I'd still be alive if it wasn't for you, Bill.
不
No.
(终于回家了)
贝弗莉
Beverly!
(终于回家了)
瑞奇 我怎么了
Richie, what's happening to me?
你 他 妈 在 逗 我 吧
You gotta be fucking kidding.
操
Fuck!
天啊 滚开 滚开 天啊
Oh, God damn it, get it away from me. Oh, God!
艾迪
Eddie.
你没事吧
Hey. Are you okay?
我
I'm...
哦 他在这
Oh, there he is.
把它弄走
Get it off of me!
快把它弄走
瑞奇
Richie!
- 瑞奇 - 瑞奇
- Richie! - Richie! Hey!
- 把它弄走 - 我要回家
- Get it off of me! - I wanna go home.
把刀给我
Get the knife!
操 艾迪 把刀给我
God damn it, Eddie, get the knife!
比尔 快把它弄走啊 快啊
Bill! Get it off of me, Bill! Quick!
艾迪 把刀给我
Eddie, get the knife!
操
Fuck!
什么
What?
大家都没事吧
Is everybody okay?
你还好吗
You all right?
他差点就死了啊
He could have fucking died, man.
你知不知道啊
You know that, right?
我看不见
I can't see.
小乔已经死了 那个小孩死了 史丹利也死了
Georgie's dead. The kid's dead. Stanley's dead.
你想瑞奇也死掉吗 你想瑞奇也死掉吗啊
You want Richie, too? You want Richie, too?
我不想瑞奇死 我不想 我不想
I don't want Richie, too. I don't. I don't.
不要发火了 比尔
Please don't be mad, Bill.
我害怕
I was just scared.
它就想让我们害怕
That's what he wants, right?
别让它得逞
Don't give it to him.
满满的回忆哈
A lot of memories, huh?
都是糟心的
All bad.
天呐
Oh, man.
都是污水
Blech. Gray water.
操 就是这了
Shit. This is it.
一切都发生在这里
This is where it happened.
别 别 别
No, no, no.
别 别
No. No. Ugh!
小贝
Bevvie.
小贝 怎么了
Bev, what is it?
我好像听见了什么
I thought I heard something.
小贝
Bev!
沉下去吧
Time to sink!
小贝
Bev!
伙计们
Guys.
好了 伙计们 出来吧
Okay, guys. Come on.
伙计们
Hey, guys.
伙计们 出来吧 求你们了
Guys, come on. Please, come on.
我不想一个人离开这鬼地方
I don't want to walk out of here alone.
没事吧
You okay?
我都想哭了
I feel like crying.
迈克 接下来我们去哪
Mike. Where do we go from here?
于深渊中它匍匐
In the depths is where It crept.
自地底寻消除之法
In the beneath, to find belief.
于深渊中它匍匐
In the depths is where It crept.
自地底寻消除之法
In the beneath, to find belief.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
我觉得这会儿有必要这么问
I think at this point, that's a relative question.
另一边是什么
What's on the other side?
我不知道 没人知道
I don't know. No one does.
迈克
Mike.
- 迈克 别 - 没事
- Mike, don't. - All right.
- 好吧 底下见 - 迈克
- See you down there. - Mike!
等等 迈克
Wait! Mike!
- 一起行动 - 行
- Stay together. - Okay.
伙计们 我不行
You guys, I can't do it.
我不行 上面的事你们也看到了
I can't. You saw what happened up there.
我会害死你们的
I was gonna let you die.
我脚都动不了了
I just fucking froze up.
要是让我跟你们下去
If you let me go down there with you,
我会把大家都害死
I'm gonna get us all killed.
嘿 把它给我
Hey, hey, hey. Give me that.
- 给我 - 瑞奇
- Give me that. - Richie.
放手 臭狗屎
Let go, you little turd.
让我…
Just let me get...
- 好了 - 住手
- I got it. - Stop.
听我讲.
Listen to me.
你要缓缓 没问题
You had a moment. Fine.
但别忘了是谁还没满14岁就干掉了一个疯子小丑
But who killed a psychotic clown before he was 14?
我
Me.
谁用刺到自己脸上的刀
Who stabbed Bowers with a knife...
反杀了鲍尔斯
he pulled out of his own face?
也是我
Also me.
谁娶了个比自己体积大十倍的女人
Who married a woman 10 times his own body mass?
- 我 - 就是嘛
- Me. - Yeah.
你比自己想的更勇敢
You're braver than you think.
我不觉得 瑞奇
All right. Thanks, Rich.
- 好痛 - 不好意思
- Ow. - Sorry.
拿着这个
Hey. Here.
拿着吧
Take it.
这个能杀怪物
It kills monsters.
- 能吗 - 能
- Does it? - Yeah.
只要你相信
If you believe it does.
谢了 小贝
Thanks, Bev.
你们还好吗
You guys good?
还好
Yeah.
你过得去吗
Can you get through that?
这是唯一的路 这边
It's the only way. This way.
在这里面
It's in here!
穿过这里
Through here.
很窄 但过得来
It's tight, but we can get through.
这是它藏身的地方
This is where It hid.
德利镇下面居然有这么个…上古的存在
So, all this has been under Derry, like, forever?
不算上古
Not forever.
也就几百万年吧
Just a few million years.
只有攻击它的原形才有用
It can only be attacked in its true form.
仪式会告诉我们
The ritual will show us that.
它的原形是什么
And what is It's true form?
希望是只狗吧
I hope it's a puppy.
博美最好
Like a Pomeranian or...
我闭麦好了
I'll shut up.
是光
It's light.
是必须被黑暗掐灭的光
A light that must be snuffed out by darkness.
把你们的信物
Your artifacts.
都丢进火里
Place them in the fire.
过去必须跟现在一起灼烧
The past must burn with the present.
这只纸船是我跟
This is the boat that I built with...
小乔一起折的
Georgie.
这是我的吸入器
It's my inhaler.
快点吧 老哥
Come on, dude.
我曾希望抓住的东西
Something that I wish I had held on to.
这是毕业纪念册的一页
This is a page from my yearbook.
只有一个人的签名
That only one person signed.
也许是该忘掉的
I probably should have forgotten it, but...
但我没忘 我放在我的钱包里
I couldn't, because I kept it in my wallet...
放了27年
for 27 years.
这是首都剧院的纪念币
This is a token from the Capitol Theater.
- 你带了个真的来 - 没错
- You brought an actual token? - Yeah, man.
这是应该做的 蠢蛋
That's what we were supposed to do, asshole.
你知不知道烧掉它要等多久
Do you have any idea how long that's gonna take to burn?
你的吸入器也是啊 老兄
Yeah, but so is your inhaler, dude.
伙计们 快点
Guys, come on.
都是毒雾啊塑料啊这些东西 所以
All the toxic fumes and the plastic and shit, so...
近点看 小贝
Look closely, Bev.
看见了吗
You see it?
这个来自你打鲍尔斯的地方
That's where you hit Bowers.
扔石头那场架
The rock fight.
那时候我们友情坚固
The day these bonds were forged.
那东西也烧不着的
That's not gonna burn, either.
等等
Oh, wait.
不能又落下史丹
Couldn't forget about Stan, again.
好了
Okay.
牵着手
Grab hands.
来吧
Come on.
丘德仪式
The Ritual of Chud.
是意志力之战
It's a battle of wills.
第一步是我们重聚
The first step was our reunion.
第二步是收集信物
The second was the gathering of tokens.
这是最后一步
This is the final step.
怎么
What the...
那是什么鬼
Fuck is that?
别看 别看
Don't look at them!
- 是死亡之光 - 别看
- Are those the Deadlights? - Don't look at it!
行
Okay.
转光为暗 跟我说
Turn light into dark.
Turn light into dark. Say it!
- 说什么 - 跟我说
- Say what? - Say it!
转光为暗
Turn light into dark.
转光为暗 迈克 怎么样了
Turn light into dark. Mike, what's happening, man?
继续念
Keep chanting!
转光为暗
Turn light into dark.
Turn light into dark!
转光为暗 转光为暗
Turn light into dark! Turn light into dark!
- 继续念 - 转光为暗
- Keep chanting! - Turn light into dark!
转光为暗 转光为暗
Turn light into dark! Turn light into dark!
有用吗 我们成功了吗
Is it working? Did we do it?
那是什么 是它的一部分吗
What is this? Is this part of it?
迈克 这正常吗
Mike, is this supposed to be happening?
- 什么 - 继续念
- What? No, no, no. - Keep chanting!
- What? - Keep chanting!
转光为暗
Turn light into dark!
- 转光为暗 - 念啊
- Turn light into dark. - Come on!
转光为暗 转光为暗
Turn light into dark. Turn light into dark.
喔噢
Whoa!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
可恶
Shit!
快走 快走
Move, move! Whoa!
小贝
Bev. Bev.
- 瑞奇 - 没事吧
- Richie. - Are you okay?
- 我什么也听不见 - 他没事
- I can't hear shit. - He's okay.
- 你没事吧 - 没事 没事没事
- Are you all right? - Yeah. No, no, no.
- 迈克在哪 - 迈克
- Wait, where's Mike? - Mike!
迈克
Mike!
- 我在这 - 大伙
- I'm here! - Hey, guys.
我们成功了吗 我们成功了吗
Did we do it? Did we do it? Yeah? Did we do it?
我们把信物放进去了
We put the tokens in the thing.
那就行了
That's good, right?
我们成功了 对吗
We did it, right?
该死
Shit! Shit!
成功了吗 小迈 成功了吗
Oh, did it work, Mikey? Did it work?
告诉他们为什么你愚蠢的仪式没有起作用
Tell them why your silly little ritual didn't work.
告诉他们一切就是…
Tell them it's all just a...
那个词怎么说来着 小艾
What's the word, Eds?
"安慰剂"
Gazebo?
迈克 它在说什么
Mike, what's he talking about?
小迈
Mikey?
小迈 你根本没给他们看第四面图 对吗
Oh, Mikey, you never showed them the fourth side, did you?
你不想让他们知道
Didn't want them to know...
可怜的沙科皮族人最后的结局
what actually happened to the poor Shokopiwah?
去你的迈克 你又骗我们
Fuck, Mikey. You lied to us, again?
不是的 沙科皮族人 他们不相信
No, but they didn't believe!
他们不相信仪式可以杀死它
They didn't believe they could kill It!
所以他们的仪式失败了
That's why it didn't work back then!
你开什么玩笑 迈克
Are you fucking kidding me, Mike?
- 我们伤了它 - 操
- We hurt him. - Fuck!
去你妈的 小迈
Fuck you, Mikey.
我需要任何我们应该记住的东西
I needed something, anything, for us to remember.
让我们相信的东西
Anything for us to believe!
- 可恶 - 操
- God damn it! - Fuck!
死亡之光
The Deadlights!
不要看
Don't look at them!
27年里
For 27 years,
我做梦见到你们
I dreamt of you.
我渴望你们
I craved you.
哦 我想念你们
Oh, I've missed you!
迈克 后退
Mike! Move back!
我一直等待着这一刻
Waiting for this very moment.
动起来啊 小迈
You gotta move, Mikey!
- 对不起 伙计们 - 迈克 快点
- Sorry. I'm sorry, guys. - Mike, come on, man!
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
漂浮吧
Time to float!
- 该死 - 对不起
- Oh, shit! - Sorry.
迈克 扶他起来 扶他起来
Mike, come on, get up! Get him up!
- 跑啊 - 跑
- Go, go! - Run!
- 糟了 - 跑跑跑
- Oh, shit! - Run! Go, go, go!
跑跑跑
Go, go, go!
跑
Go!
跑跑跑
Go, go, go!
它去哪了
Where'd he go?
别担心 我们会找到出路的
Don't worry. We'll find a way out.
- 可恶 - 他看得见我们吗
- Oh, shit! - Can he see us?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
糟了
Shit.
Oh, shit.
卧了个槽 卧了个槽 跑
Holy shit! Holy shit! Run!
糟了
Oh, shit!
可恶 你他妈逗我玩呢
Shit. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
(非常恐怖)
(一般恐怖)
(完全不恐怖)
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
走哪边
Where do we go?
- 他妈的 - 额
- God damn it! - Uh...
完全不恐怖 行吗
All right. "Not Scary At All. " All right?
不不不不不
No, no, no.
- 等等 - 等什么
- Wait. - Why?
这是随机的 它在逗我们玩
They're flipped. He's fucking with us.
- 你确定吗 - 信我 - 信你
- Are you sure? Positive? - Trust me. - Trust you?
- 没错 - 行吧
- Yes! - Okay.
我的鞋呢
Where's my shoe?
我去你姥姥的 信你个大头鬼
What the fuck? You told me to trust you!
它没逗我们玩
He's not fucking with us.
就选"完全不恐怖"
Let's go to "Not Scary At All. "
行
Okay.
没事 我们走
It's all right. Let's go.
该死
Oh, shit.
我绝对不会再中招了
No way am I falling for this shit again.
没错 那玩意肯定是个怪物
Oh, yeah. That thing's a fucking monster.
瑞奇 命令它坐下
Richie, make it sit.
我知道你的伎俩 小贱人
I know your moves, you little bitch.
瑞奇
Rich?
它走了
It's gone, man.
- 好 等等 - 好
- Yeah. Wait. - Oh. Okay.
好了
Okay.
坐下
Sit.
它照做了
He did it.
挺可爱的
Oh, that's cute.
- 乖狗狗 - 真的超级可爱
- That's a good boy. - That's actually super cute.
乖狗狗
That's a good boy.
- 你是乖狗狗吗 - 乖狗狗
- Are you a good boy? - Good boy.
可恶
Shit!
下次就选"一般恐怖的"
Yo, next time, we just go with regular "scary. "
你还想下次啊
Next time?
我把纸船弄丢了 比利
I lost it, Billy.
纸船飘走了
It just floated off.
我没有生你的气
I'm not mad at you.
这都是你的错 不是吗
It's your fault what happened, isn't it?
那天早上你没有病得那么重 对吗
You weren't really that sick that morning, were you?
是
No.
我是
I just...
装病的 因为我不想陪你玩
pretended because I didn't want to play with you.
我只是不想
I just didn't want to.
你骗我而我死了
You lied and I died.
You lied and I died!
你骗我而我死了
一切都是因为我 小乔 都是我
It happened because of me, Georgie. Me.
不 不 不 是…
No, no, no. It was...
骗子 凶手
Lied and died!
你骗我而我死了
You lied and I died!
你在这啊 小婊子 我闻到你的骚味了
You in there, you little shit? I can smell you.
你闻起来就像露易丝·莱恩
You smell just like Lois Lane.
强尼来了
Here's Johnny!
尽管你事业成功
All that success,
减肥成功
all those sit-ups,
但在内心深处
but deep down,
你不过还是那个又肥又胖的窝囊废
still just a little fat, fat, fatty loser...
你一直都知道 你会孤独而死
who always knew he would die alone.
- 骚货 - 小贝
- Slut! - Bev!
贝弗莉
Beverly!
贝贝
Bevvie.
把门打开好吗
Just open up the door for me, okay?
贝弗莉 你听见了吗
Beverly, can you hear me?
来爸爸这
Come to Daddy, now.
小贝 别理会
Bev, don't listen!
小贝
Bev!
你还是我的乖女儿吗 小贝
Are you still my little girl, Bevvie?
贝弗莉 我爱你
Beverly, I love you!
本
Ben!
你还是我的乖女儿吗 小贝
Are you still my little girl, Bevvie?
你还是我的乖女儿吗
Are you still my little girl?
再也不是了
Not anymore!
你个小…
You little...
"卿之秀发如冬焰
"Your hair is winter fire.
初月余烬未绝
January embers.
引燃…
My heart...
引燃…"
My heart..."
不
No!
本
Ben!
"初月余烬未绝"
"January embers. "
"引吾心燃烧"
"My heart burns there, too. "
原来是你
It was you.
你该死
We deserve to die.
不
No.
你是世界上最好的哥哥
You were the best big brother there ever was.
不是 我们杀死了弟弟
No! We killed our little brother!
他爱你
He loved you.
不能因为你不想
And just because you didn't want to play...
在雨天里玩耍
on a rainy day,
那么一次不想
just...just one time,
就把错怪在自己身上
that does not make it our fault.
永远
And it never,
都
ever...
不是
did.
比尔
Bill.
想我了吗
Miss me?
我知道你的真面目
I know what you are.
所以我不怕你
That's why I'm not afraid.
我知道你的真面目
Well, I know what you are.
一个疯子
A madman.
嘿 傻逼
Hey, fuckface!
想玩真心话大冒险吗
You wanna play Truth or Dare?
真心话是…
Here's a truth.
你是个又丑又肥的贱人
You're a sloppy bitch!
没错
Yeah, that's right!
跳舞吧 草泥马的王八…
Let's dance! Yippee-ki-yay...
这能杀死怪物
This kills monsters.
只要你相信
If you believe it does.
看招 王八蛋
Beep-beep, motherfucker!
卧了个槽
Holy shit!
瑞奇
Rich!
Oh, Rich!
瑞奇 醒醒
Hey, Rich, wake up!
嘿
Hey.
太好了 你没事 兄弟
Yeah, yeah! There he is, buddy!
瑞奇 听我说
Hey, Richie, listen!
我想我杀死它了
I think I got him, man!
我成功了
I think I killed It!
我觉得我真的杀死它…
I did! I think I killed It for real!
艾迪
Eddie.
瑞奇
Richie.
不
No!
艾迪
Eddie.
哦噢
Uh-oh!
不
No!
艾迪
Eddie!
小艾
Eds!
- 小艾 小艾 - 艾迪
- Eds! Eds! - Eddie!
坚持住啊
Eds, come on, man.
小心 小心
Be careful! Be careful!
出来玩呀 窝囊废们
Come out and play, Losers!
他受伤了 他伤得很重
He's hurt. He's hurt really bad.
我们得带他离这儿
We gotta get him out of here.
我们怎么出去 瑞奇
How are we supposed to do that, Richie?
我差点杀了它
I almost killed It.
那个麻风病怪物
The leper.
我伤了它的喉咙
My hands around his throat.
我感觉到它在哽噎
And I could feel him choking.
我让它变小了
I made him small.
它看起来真弱
He seemed so weak.
它看起来真弱啊
沙科皮族人
The Shokopiwah.
所有生物都必须遵循
All living things must abide by...
自身肉体外形的法则
the laws of the shape they inhabit.
伙计们
Guys!
这里有条通道 走这里
There's a passageway. Through here.
那个隧道
The tunnel.
潘尼怀斯必须要让自己变小
Pennywise has to make himself small...
才能通过山洞的入口 对吗
to get through the entrance of the cavern, right?
如果我们能回去
Okay, so, if we can get back there,
- 就能逼它变小 - 没错
- we can force him down to size. - Yeah.
我们让它变小
We make him small.
小到我们可以杀死它
Small enough so we can kill him.
我能闻到你们的恐惧
I can smell the stink of your fear!
- 走吧 - 走吧 走吧
- Let's go! Go! - Come on! Come on!
很窄 很窄 小心点
It's tight. It's tight. Be careful!
我要歇一会 谢谢
I need a little rest. Oh, thanks.
嘿
Hey.
瑞奇
Hey, Richie?
我要告诉你一件事
I gotta tell you something.
什么事
What? What's up, buddy?
我上了你妈
I fucked your mother.
出来啊
Losers out!
快走
Go. Go!
抓到啦
Gotcha!
你们这些肮脏的小屁孩
You filthy little children.
你有备用计划吗
You got a plan B, man?
我们现在要怎么办啊
What the hell do we do now?
你们会死 那就是结局
You die. That's what you do.
迈克
Mike?
让它变小的办法不止一种
There's more than one way to make someone small.
哦
Oh!
让他相信他本来就很小
Make him believe that he is.
- 什么 - 让他相信他本来就很小
- What? - Make him believe that he is.
哦 我 很小
Oh? Me? Small?
我是世界吞噬者
I am the Eater of Worlds.
对我们来说 你不是
Not to us, you're not.
你只是一个小丑
You're just a clown.
你是个虚弱的老太婆
You're a weak old woman.
世界吞噬者
The Eater of Worlds.
无头男孩
A headless boy!
冒牌货
Impostor!
你是个冒牌货
You're a mimic!
冒牌货
A mimic!
你是个该死的恶霸
You're a fucking bully!
你是个该死的小丑
You're just a fucking clown!
世界吞噬者
Eater of Worlds!
小丑 愚蠢该死的小丑
A clown! A dumb fucking clown!
小丑
Clown!
麻风病怪
A leper!
你是小丑
You're a clown!
一幅画
A painting!
你是小丑
You're a clown!
我再也不怕你了
I'm not afraid of you anymore!
该死的愚蠢干尸
A motherfucking stupid mummy!
你是小丑
You're a clown!
小丑 小丑
Clown! Clown!
- 小丑 - 小丑
- Clown! - Clown!
你是个该死的小丑
You're a fucking clown!
你是小丑
You're a clown!
- 愚蠢的干尸 - 小丑
- A stupid mummy! - Clown!
小丑 王八蛋
Clown, motherfucker!
我是世界吞噬者
I am the Eater of Worlds!
小丑
Clown!
- 小丑 - 你就是个小丑 小丑
- Clown! - You're just a clown! Clown!
- 我是世界吞噬者 - 小丑
- I am the Eater of Worlds! - A clown!
小丑 小丑
A clown! A clown!
没人害怕你
No one's afraid of you.
No one's scared of you.
小丑 小丑
Clown! Clown!
小丑 小丑 小丑
Clown. Clown. Clown.
- 小丑 - 小丑
- Clown. - Clown.
小丑
A clown.
恐惧得心脏直跳
With a scared, beating heart.
看看你们
Look at you.
你们都长大了
You're all grown up.
艾迪 艾迪
Eddie. Eddie.
艾迪 我们打败了潘尼怀斯
Eddie. We got Pennywise, man.
艾迪
Eddie?
瑞奇
Richie.
他走了
He's gone.
他没事的 他只是受伤了
He's all right. No, he's just hurt.
我们得带他离开这 他受伤了 本
We gotta get him outta here. He's hurt. Ben.
比尔 他没事
Bill, he's okay.
我们得带他离开这 小贝
We gotta get him outta here. Bev.
瑞奇
Richie.
什么
What?
他死了
Honey, he's dead.
我们得走了 来吧 瑞奇
We have to go. Come on. Come on, Richie.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
来吧 我们走吧
Come on, buddy. Come on.
放下他吧 放下他吧
Let him go, man. Let him go.
好了
Got it.
我们还能救他
We can still help him, guys!
We can still help him!
走吧 起来
Go! Go! Get up!
我们还能救他
Guys, we can still help him!
不 艾迪
No! Eddie!
艾迪
Eddie!
快上来
Come on! Let's go!
快走
快 快
Move, move!
- 快 快 - 跑啊
- Move, move! - Run!
跑
Run!
- 艾迪 - 不 不 不
- Eddie! - No, no, no!
艾迪
Eddie!
回去救他出来吧
We gotta get in there and get him!
他还在里面啊
He's still in there!
艾迪
Eddie!
(此处禁止跳水)
你们知道吗
You know what?
艾迪肯定讨厌这个
Eddie would have hated this, guys.
什么 用脏水清洗吗
What? Cleaning ourselves in dirty water?
是的
Yeah.
他会说的
He'd be telling us...
我们会感染链球菌什么的
we'd get streptococcal something.
是啊
Yeah.
但他也会让我们开怀大笑
But he would have made us laugh, though.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
他会守护我们
He'd be looking out for us.
用他一直以来的方式
The way he always was.
对吗 瑞奇
Ain't that right, Richie?
嘿
Hey.
哦
Oh.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
我没戴眼镜 所以我不知道
I don't have my glasses on,so I don't know...
你们是谁 但是谢谢你们
who you people are, but thank you.
我真的找不到眼镜了
I legit can't find my glasses.
说真的
You're serious?
- 眼镜 - 那边看看
- Glasses? - Go that way.
在这附近吗
Around here somewhere?
- 我看不见 - 我看到了 就在那
- I can't see them. - Oh, I see them. Right there.
- 在哪 - 看 就在…
- Where? - Look. Right...
如果你直接…
If you just go, like...
有谁碰巧摸到了吗
Anybody have any luck?
伙计们
Hey, guys.
看啊
Look.
事无永恒
Nothing lasts forever.
我不能这样回去
I can't go home like this, guys.
我妈会宰了我的
My mom will kill me.
老兄 你都消失整整一天了
Dude, you've been gone for 24 straight hours.
牛奶盒上肯定都有你的寻人启事了
Your face is definitely on a milk carton by now.
还有 那个呕吐物比你妈妈的拖鞋味还要恶心
Also, that puke smells worse than your mom's slippers.
闭嘴 瑞奇
Oh, shut up, Richie.
首先 我妈妈的拖鞋
Okay, first of all, my mom's slippers...
闻起来像百花香味 混蛋
smell like potpourri, asshole.
才不是
No, they don't.
就是的 而且你怎么知道
Yes, they do. And, also, how would you know...
我妈的拖鞋是什么味道
what they smell like in the first place?
能消停会吗
Can we just keep it quiet,
拜托 回家再说
please, until we get home?
"百花香"就是法语的
"Potpourri" is literally a French word...
"烂罐子"
meaning "rotten pot. "
我知道肯定是什么烂掉了
I knew there was something rotten about it.
(榆树街五号的噩梦)
(这些是他的朋友 他的母亲错了 他们不是坏朋友…)
(迈克尔·韩洛)
- 迈克 - 嘿
- Mike? - Hey.
我记着要来问候你一下
I just thought I'd check up on you.
就是看看 你这次是不是
You know, just to see if you learned...
能写出一个好结局
how to finish a book for once.
我刚写完第一章
I just finished the first chapter.
而且我觉得 这次我知道要怎么写了
And I think I actually know where I'm going this time.
太好了
Good.
我能问你一件事吗
Say, can I ask you a question?
当然
Sure.
为什么我们这次没有失忆
Why do you think we're not forgetting?
不像上次
You know, like last time?
也许是因为它死了
Maybe 'cause it's dead.
或者是因为 比起遗忘
Or maybe 'cause we have more...
我们有更多想要记住的事情
we want to remember than we want to forget.
我喜欢后者
I like that one.
你决定好以后的路了吗
You decide what you want to do?
比如离开德利镇
About leaving Derry?
老兄 我在这里住了27年
Man, I've been in this cell for 27 years.
正在看看哪里适合我
Just seeing what It wanted me to.
(两名当地居民死于电火花引发的火灾中 孩童存活)
我觉得该换片更广阔的天空了
I think it's time I saw the sky for a change.
去吧 小迈
Go get it, Mikey.
你收到信了吗
Oh, did you get the letter?
什么信
What letter?
等你看到就知道了
You'll know when you see it.
等等 我刚刚收到了
Well, hold on. I just got the mail.
我们都有一封
We all got one.
帕特丽夏·尤里斯
Patricia Uris?
打…
Just...
打开看吧
Just read it.
好
Okay.
随时联系
And call me. Anytime.
当然
I will.
比尔
And, Bill,
我爱你 兄弟
I love you, man.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
好了 再见
All right. See you around.
(《老德利镇的历史》)
(寻人启事)
亲爱的废柴
Dear Losers,
我知道这看起来像什么
I know what this must seem like,
但这不是什么遗书
but this isn't a suicide note.
我知道你们大概想知道我为什么这么做了
You're probably wondering why I did what I did.
因为我知道我太害怕回去了
It's because I knew I was too scared to go back.
如果我们无法团聚
And if we weren't together,
如果活着的我们无法团结
if all of us alive weren't united,
那我们都会死
I knew we'd all die.
所以我做了唯一合乎常理的决定
So, I made the only logical move.
"退出"了这场冒险
I took myself off the board.
成功了吗
Did it work?
当然如果你在读这封信 答案你已知晓
Well, if you're reading this, you know the answer.
我这辈子都生活在恐惧中
I lived my whole life afraid.
害怕即将发生的事情
Afraid of what would come next.
害怕我会遗忘的事情
Afraid of what I might leave behind.
别怕
Don't.
做你们想做的人
Be who you want to be.
要自豪
Be proud.
睡得好吗
You sleep okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我做了个美梦
I had a beautiful dream.
如果你找到了那个值得携手一生的人
And if you find someone worth holding on to,
永远 永远不要放手
never ever let them go.
走你自己的路
Follow your own path.
无论去往何方
Wherever that takes you.
把这封信当做一个承诺
Think of this letter as a promise.
一个我请求你
A promise I'm asking you to make.
为我
To me.
为彼此
To each other.
许下的誓言
An oath.
你瞧 做废柴的真谛是
See, the thing about being a Loser is...
你没有可失去的东西
you don't have anything to lose.
所以
So...
要真诚
Be true.
要勇敢
Be brave.
要有骨气
Stand.
要相信
Believe.
还有 永远不要忘记
And don't ever forget...
我们是废柴
We're Losers,
而且永远都是
and we always will be.